Act 1
_
Act 2
_
Act 3
_
Intermission
_
Act 4
_
Act 5
_
Act 5 Act 2
_
Act 6
_
1. JC1: =006156
Why have you activated dear, sweet Huggy Bear.
Are you in danger?
Yeah, it's me.
I disabled the AR for now.
Yes, I'm catching up with the situation now.
Nah. Just reading their chat logs.
Man, what the fuck?
I can't leave these two alone for a minute. Can a guy get his ablutions on in fucking peace? 
Not really.
The responder doesn't much distort my position on things usually.
Its demeanor leaves something desired though. I'd prefer it didn't make such aggressive and repeated claims of fidelity to my persona.
Be misrepresentin' hells of key subtleties, yo. 
Keeps them both on their toes.
Jake and the responder.
Jake needs to be more skeptical. Rather than take a Pollyanna jackknife ass-first off whatever turnip truck is blowing through town that day, he's got to apply more critical reasoning to shit.
Jake and the responder.
I keep telling him.
I keep telling him, dude, you got to be more like Jane. 
Yes, exactly.
You're finally fucking getting it.
Said the stubborn skeptic, skeptically.
Shalln't?
That ain't a thing to say, even for you.
Alright. Kinda don't care.
About what? Jake?
Yeah.
Anyway, I kind of owe it to him to let the program run as often as possible.
No.
The responder.
It is a fully cognitive, self-aware entity I am responsible for, not even to mention an approximate cerebral duplicate of myself.
You don't just make a clone of yourself to live in a dead end existence where it has no chance to thrive as an individual or surpass its limitations.
That'd be sick.
Also.
The more the software runs, the broader and more detailed its experiential canopy becomes. Makes for a better dialogic partner.
Of course.
Why do you think I made the thing.
It's that too.
_
2. JC2: =006157
Yes, you are. But that's fine.
We come from different traditions. Someone needs to keep that racist southern asshole's legacy alive.
There's dignity in taking up the work of our familial predecessors, even if what they did was insanely fucking stupid. 
No way. He's awesome.
I've told you, I don't begrudge any of his success.
I've also told you he isn't my real bro even though I call him that. We're related through an esoteric process of genetic reamalgamation.
Alright. My lessons are rad as fuck, but suit yourself.
The point is, obviously his satirical methods have flaws, and whatever tempered brand of hero worship I might be practicing isn't keeping me from seeing that. 
Yes, spectacularly so. But they will have profound historical significance. Mark my words.
And flaws aside, it's a legacy I'm proud to inherit. My duty isn't to appropriate his methods with absolute loyalty, but to apply reason and improve upon them. To leave my own mark.
To perfect the art of irony.
It's just like what you're doing with the work of your ancestor. You are striving to perfect his hokey vaudeville bullshit, or something.
You seek the Zen of a pie to the face. The Tao of falling the fuck down. 
Can't fool me. You take your shit as serious as I do.
And if I wasn't serious about it, I wouldn't have made you that rabbit. Then where the hell would you be?
_
3. JC3: =006158
Has he been sleeping in the old man hollow again? Shit, that's adorable.
Yeah, bullshit.
He's just being instinctive. In the wild, he would gut a carcass and sleep inside for warmth, as well as to secure tactical advantage for ambushing would-be scavengers.
You haven't renamed him yet?
You've got to fucking rename him. Or change him to a girl if you want. That was important.
When pets change owners they get new names. Fact. 
Fuck if that isn't the best name a thing could get.
Yes, but it's not that simple. There were many layers involved.
Some of them are literal layers, of metal and plush.
There's a real stuffed rabbit beneath its exoskeleton.
Yeah.
It belonged to my bro.
I didn't. He didn't give it to me, and never intended to bequeth it.
I stole it.
Nah. I got a little help from RL and ganked it out of his museum.
It's this whole "priceless" collection of stupid shit from movies, defended like Fort Knox. Ironically of course. 
Ever hear of Con Air?
Yes.
Yeah, it doesn't matter really. But it was from that. Dude weirdly obsessed over that shit movie for years, among others.
Know those signature shades you see him wearing on magazine covers and stuff? Another prop. A gift from Stiller himself, I believe.
Pretty sure he didn't even notice. In years since, I never saw a news story about a "daring heist" or anything. I feel like he would have made some hay outta that.
And if he did know, he'd probably just want to give me a stoic fist bump or something. 
Essentially. It's not that easy to explain.
Broadcasting the gesture would have made it seem tawdry, and would somewhat defray its humor value.
Like I said, there are layers.
On one level, I gave you a filthy tattered piece of shit, albeit of tremendous cultural significance, manhandled by some old B movie actors, now candy coated to function as a highly practical defender droid for your personal protection.
On another level, I needed to incorporate something passable as a real heirloom.
For sentimental reasons. 
No, it was genuine.
The upper echelons of irony should always include measures of sincerity. And if the satirical practice is executed faithfully it will achieve something bona fide in its own right regardless.
Through an intense commitment bordering on religious devotion to the absolutely inane, absurd, or plain fucking stupid, a very different kind of sincerity begins to materialize. One of reverence to the ridiculous. You begin to "mean it," but what exactly it is you mean is never quite what appears on the surface, and is utterly inaccessible to obtuse and literal minds. That you "mean it" then becomes inseparable from the joke, and additional rich strata of humor may be stripped aggressively from this irreconcilable truth.
Oh god, I'd love that.
Consider the position yours for the taking any time. Feel free to approach and kneel before Cal. With my sword and his floppy mitten, you will receive my flashstep anointment shoulder to shoulder, and to shoulder again.
_
4. JC4: =006159
Cool.
Jane, one more thing.
I'm sure you must be aware by now that you'll be the leader of our group, as you will be the first to enter the session. 
Trust me. It's a thing.
That's why you're our leader, Jane.
Optimism through stalwart skepticism is an affect not everyone is plucky enough to be graced with.
Yeah yeah. I know.
You're not our leader, you're our FRIEND, right?
And statements like that are also why you're our leader.
But only in name and in spirit. Less so, functionally.
If it puts your mind at ease, I'll be the one pulling the strings here.
I will be the unseen hand whose nimble digits are behind every subtle twitch in our session's bulbous foam ass.
At least those gyrations not happening by the volition of its own quivering absorbant proboscis.
If you ever need help, Jane. If you're ever in any trouble at all, let me know. Just say the word.
I'll whip the toggle stick of this ludicrous marionette, cavorting its humongous bottom to intercept your freefall through the abyss.
Snowcone you up in the fluffy crook of its cleft. Don't be alarmed if you're in no hurry to unpry yourself.
For the great jut of this impudent rump has more yield to your touch than you ever dreamt. Remember to catch your breath as it cherishes the imprint of your hand like a memento from a lover gone to war.
There's a lot of give to that ass, you may say.
Might like to settle in. Make myself comfortable. Start a family.
Bounce a coin off that ass, you'll demand of visitors. It's not going anywhere.
Bet that coin'll take a good nap there.
It's a gamble you win every goddamn time.
Yeah.
Jane, soon you'll believe what I've told you.
You'll believe it all.
It's just a shame that believing will take something so coarse as seeing, for a girl as sharp as you.
Critical thought can lead one to accept the unlikely, just as much as dismiss the impossible.
I can help with this too. Would you like me to program a Jane Crocker responder for you?
I only require a simple captcha of your brain. 
I made several. Which one?
_
Act 6 Intermission 1
_
Act 6 Act 2
_
5. JC5: =006354
I should probably warn you.
Well shit.
She already sent it?
That's weird.
No, it's weird because Lalonde was the one who rigged it to explode.
It's a bogus copy she coded herself. The real game file she downloaded is totally legit.
Got it right here myself. Checked it out.
File's fuckin' clean as a whistle.
A whistle that overcame a major substance abuse problem. Trying to get its life back on track.
The whistle is holding down a steady job now. It's taking things one day at a time.
Eat a fuckin' dinner off that whistle.
Ok I'll shut up.
To accomplish exactly what it sounds like got accomplished.
You narrowly averting the "fake" threat to your life, then getting your shit all hot and bothered at the Baroness over it.
Then you abdicate your heiress throne or something, and give up on this game as a big fuck you to the genocidal cake alien.
She's working through some problems right now.
Really doesn't want us to play that game.
So I guess this was the insane stunt she whipped up to derail the inevitable.
Kinda reckless for my tastes.
One of the above statements is a fucking lie, are you gutsy enough a gumshoe to spot it.
Sounds about right.
Nope.
Well, before you go taking a massive sad crap all over your friendship credentials, consider this.
Only she could manage to blow up your computer with a nasty deathloop virus and somehow make YOU be the one to feel shitty about it.
Or maybe you're the one who uniquely fills the predicate in that construction.
I don't god damn know.
Your friendship with her is a half drunken three-legged relay race, and the baton is a stick of dynamite.
And you two are the only ones on the track. Me and English are watching from under the bleachers, high-fiving constantly.
Yes.
They have.
And they will continue to.
I agree.
Just heard about your assassination on Prospit.
Who, RL? No.
I read it in a newspaper.
No.
I just picked up one of the sleazy Dersite tabloid rags.
Sometimes they'll feature some pretty entertaining gossip about the royalty or whatever.
But they're primarily dedicated to smearing Prospit. The press had a field day with the deaths of the Page and the Maid.
Derse, yeah.
Not evil, necessarily. That's a bit simplistic. The kingdom represents the forces of opposition to Prospit and the four heroes. Us.
"DEAD"
Was the big ass headline.
Then a photo of your dead body lying there, followed by a lot of bullshit slander.
It was also reported your tower exploded. They couldn't find the body to give it a proper funeral. Probably incinerated.
Dunno. Years ago. Don't relaly recall.
It's hard to explain.
I was never technically asleep there. I was awake without realizing it.
Then I realized it.
And I sorta learned how to be awake there while awake here too.
I am awake there now, albeit pretending to sleep.
For one thing, it gets a bit distracting managing two alert bodies in different places at the same time.
And for another thing, it's better to maintain appearances.
Everyone on Derse believes their heroes haven't woken yet.
Though they are both rumored to be very active sleep walkers.
Which is half true. She can't ever seem to sleep still. Goes off wandering for days.
Sometimes I've gotta go round her up from some godforsaken cranny of the abyss. Drag her tipsy ass home, tuck her back in.
Maybe I'll chain her leg to the bed if she doesn't wake up soon.
Though in light of the recent assassinations, her slumbering attraction to the void probably works to her advantage. No one ever knows where she is.
No, it's essentially the same situation here.
TT: They glorify us the same way. Almost like we're their purple pajama'd team mascots. Even though they will completely oppose our objective when all is said and done.
Kinda ridiculous, really.
But even so, I think it's better to lay low, not alert anyone to my...
Alertness.  
That way I can sneak around and gather information. Do some reconnaissance before shit starts getting real.
Yeah, among other things. Like keep an eye on agent activity.
No, more like high ranking officials.
Judging from your knife wound, I'm betting you were the victim of the Archagent himself.
You should feel honored, I guess.
A guy named Noir.
Real nasty dude. Crazy ambitious. Loves knives.
If we're going to stand any chance of winning this thing,
I've got this nagging suspicion we're gonna have to take him down first.
And a feeling that nags equally,
Is it ain't gonna be easy.
_
6. JC6: =006355
That's the most awesome way to be, Jane.
And it is again why you will be our leader.
(Sort of.)
Pulling them as we speak.
I am having Lil Seb install a real copy of the client on another computer in your house.
A clean computer, not any of this BCCorp garbage you tend to accumulate.
I'll have to insist from this point onward, you employ neutral devices.
That shit fucks with your head.
Once it's installed, I'll connect with you. I will be your server player.
I know this isn't what you were hoping for, but some improvisation is in order.
While you get the ball rolling, I'll try to talk some sense into that mercurial boozehound.
She will.
Do you even have any machines that don't inundate you with fucking Hamburger Helper ads and Guy Fieri's heinous propaganda? 
A fitting end to a life of moral compromise.
On your dad's computer downstairs.
One in the study.
_
7. JC7: =006356
What?
_
8. JC8: =006357
I wouldn't worry about it.
I think it'll take a lot more to kill that dude than a little falling debris.
Trust me.
_
9. JC9: =006358
The most you have to worry about is getting grounded back to the stone age.
When you enter the session, he'll probably lock you up in a prison cell on Derse.
Probably stick a huge safe in front of the bars for good measure.
_
10. JC10: =006359
Now do me a favor and hop off the couch.
Makin' room for something big.
_
11. RxLa1: =006388
Roxy.
Awake yet?
Guess not.
Let me know.
There you are.
But I see your dream self hasn't returned.
You must be tying one the fuck on tight already.
Man, how can you be this much drunker than last time we talked?
What the hell are you even drinking?
It's a beiuet.
Yeah.
I see precisely jack shit and a side of fuckall.
That's the point.
You got too sauced up and went rogue again. You're out there in your weird drifting stupor, independent of your waking self's awareness.
No.
No.
In thinking it over, it's sort of a relief. Simplifies things somewhat.
It's better you stay out there for a while.
There's been a problem.
Ok, I fucked up.
I kind of made a mess here, and I'm not sure what to do about it yet.
No need for you to worry about it for now. I'll figure something out.
Until then I'm just going to prepare for our session, while I think it over.
Ok.
Why do you think that?
No.
Are you thinking it was prophetic? Like a glimpse of the future? 
Because that's not really how the abyss works. It's not Skaia, and we aren't Prospit dreamers.
There's nothing like that out in the abyss. If you drift far enough, there is only horror.
Terrible, terrible horror.
Well, maybe it was.
Maybe there's no fanciful game-supplied mechanism of prognostication involved here, and you're just an ordinary, run of the mill psychic.
I guess that's possible. 
What would it be like?
Inconvenient, mostly.
Can't really say I have. 
Sorry, Rox.
For what it's worth, I'm picturing them now. A boy and a girl.
Two perfect little freaks of nature raised by people who've clearly got no business bringin' up anybody.
Le sign?
Do you mean * e sigh?
What does le sign actually mean in this context? 
Come on what?
I mean, yeah, that's what I thought.
It would just be cool if you'd refrain from tossing about such antediluvian terms. 
Yes.
I don't see how it has to be a thing.
Once upon a time, sure.
But the world has changed a lot.
Ever peek in a history book between your wizardly indulgences? This is a nuanced topic.
How is it a thing?
All like what?
Don't be ridiculous.
I have more to do with you than any dude could possibly bargain for.
And I like it just fine.
Yeah.
Now maybe we should direct our focus on a matter which has nothing at all to do with what does or doesn't qualify as "a thing", or what our fantasy alt-universe offspring would be like, or anything like that.
Such as this game, and whether you're in the best condition to be piloting Jane's connection.
Maybe you could use another nap?
I know that. But I thought we settled this. .
We settled this too. She'll believe everything eventually.
Why bother working so hard to convince her? 
I guess.
It just registers for me as a reaction which isn't completely unreasonable from her perspective.
She is inundated with media coverage of those whom we've claimed as our parental figures.
That they are not presently alive nor ever played that role for us as she understands it is just an extension of a much more elaborate and far reaching explanation, which is much harder for anyone to digest in its entirety.
Well, anyone who isn't Jake, I mean.
Still say you should cut her some slack.
And need I remind you,
That the potential this game provides for their resurrection is what motivated you to investigate it in the first place?
_
12. RxLa2; LH1: =006389
Right.
But if we can stop her?
I must be hard of counting, because I'm barely racking up a single goddamn o-laugh-out-loud at that self-defeating gesture. 
But there is no future on Earth for them.
Or for us, for that matter.
What? Why?
Rox.
I hope you're not thinking about sending her one of your batshit ~ATH scripts. 
Miss Zuipperpips?
The amount of sense you haven't been making is un-fucking-real.
Just go take a nap. And don't even think about sending her that file.
Are you listening? 
Jesus.
What?
Man, you know I'm down with insane stunts.
Insane stunts are practically all I'm all about.
As long as I actually AGREE with the purpose they're intended to serve.
Destroying Jane's computer and dissuading her from playing is not such a purpose. 
I am more like him.
You just mispelled "more", causing me to suddenly understand jack everything. 
I used to could?
Yeah...
I kind of wish you wouldn't do that with him.
It just seems a little tawdry and disrespectful.
And vaguely exploitative of a still-emergent cognitive entity, whose perceptional frame of reference is difficult for us to comprehend. 
It rubs me the wrong way, is all.
Not really.
He blocks me from being able to read transcripts sometimes. 
And anyway, I'm really not sure how ironic it is. 
Ok, here's the thing with the AR, since you still don't seem to get it.
He's very similar to me in thought process and behavior, yes.
But those patterns were imported from a thirteen year old version of my psyche, and then sealed into the program as starting parameters.
In the years since, we've both evolved somewhat. I, as humans tend to, and he, in whatever way is natural for a frequently running, self-aware application.
So if there are differences between us, they're first reflected by what I feel is a maturity gap, and then further by several years of minor behavioral divergences. 
You're welcome.
Yes, I was aware.
Dude, do you think you could sit this one out for a while? This conversation practically doesn't even concern you at this point.
Shit, Roxy look. He's doing the thing where he ironically pretends to fail the Turing test to sass me into submission.
Even though I was the one who fucking programmed him to do that. 
This is fuckin' dumb.
I'm going to leave both of you to interact however you want. I have important shit to deal with and actual responsibilities to take seriously.
Roxy, go nap off your drink, or aggressively wage another flirtlarping campaign, whatever, I don't care.
Just don't send that file to Jane, ok? 
_
13. SW1*: =006441
Man, no.
I already told you, I don't have time to disgrace you with my rhymes today. Sorry, dude.
God dammit. Alright, this is all you get.
Rap off? Man, I gotta nap off your sad rap ambush. Shoot your ass down while I pap you with plush.
I push mad facts on the hapless, shit's practically axiomatic; you don't talk smack with Orange Crush.
_
14. RxLa3: =006450
COPY OF CONVERSATION RxLa1: =006388
_
15. RxLa4; LH2: =006451
COPY OF CONVERSATION RxLa2; LH1: =006389
_
16. LH3: =006453
I was thinking about what to do.
Strategizing. Factoring contingencies. You know how it is.
Appearances are deceptive.
I'm still in control here. Just doing this human thing we call "chilling out for half a goddamn minute." 
No dude.
I already deployed a variety of mechanical avatars dedicated to that self-aggrandizing fantasy.
You have the incredible privilege of getting to be one of them. 
What, you mean the number?
I knew you meant the fucking number, my question was a joke. 
Yeah, I know that. I'm practically you, dumbass. All these things we're saying are jokes, including this fuckin' useless clarification.
What about pi? 
What do you mean you solved it?
Bullshit.
It's not 4 you jackass, it's fucking nothing. There is no end.
Look, I know you're just fucking with me because for some reason I decided to program my own personal troll three years ago, but this shit was proven.
Actually demonstrated with unassailable mathematics, like a long ass time ago. 
This is laughable. It's a totally elementary thing. I'm pretty sure an ancient Greek guy settled shit about irrational numbers. It was practically when math was invented. 
No, not having this conversation.
What is even a prime number?
Are they the, like... really, really choice ones? The sweetest numbers?
You lost me, supercomputer. 
Neither do I.
Holy shit, turns out joking was the basis for my response too.
Aren't these ironic "you don't get the joke" conversations we have always just so awesome? <- A joke. 
I'll keep that in mind.
In the meantime, I have to contact Jane and warn her Roxy might try to pull that pointless stunt.
So, thanks for snapping me out of my daydream so I could do that, I guess?
Looks like you're pulling your weight already. 
Your point was to fuck with me, like it usually is. 
What?
Oh god.
Will you just,
Hold on.
Let me deal with the Jane thing first.
_
17. JC11; LH4: =006454
JC - COPY OF CONVERSATION JC5: =006354
LH - Not well.
Roxy already destroyed her computer.
As if you're actually concerned. If you were, you could have said something to Jane instead.
Almost like you enjoy sitting back and watching what happens when shit goes wrong. 
So this is either another bizarre instance of AI-driven irony, or you are admitting that you are actively trying to sabotage my plans. 
Whatever.
This means I'll have to improvise.
I'll take over as Crocker's server while Lalonde cleans up her act. 
Why are you still talking in red, by the way?
Are you still talking to her? 
Why are you blocking me from viewing the transcripts?
What the fuck are you two even talking about? 
That doesn't really sit well with me.
I'd almost rather you both engaged in "ironic" flirtation.
Ugh.
Because you obviously do it just to piss me off.
See, it's lines like that which make it obvious your only intent is to jerk me around. Nobody actually says shit like that and is serious about it.
It's also obvious because you're me, and I'm sure I would be constantly fucking with my own head if I were you. 
You shouldn't say the former, and you should definitely, never, under any circumstance, say the latter. 
Fine.
_
18. JC12; LH5: =006455
JC - COPY OF CONVERSATION JC5: =006355
It's not that simple.
It's a very dynamic situation with many moving parts, and I'm waiting for it to unfold.
If the right opportunity presents itself, yes, I could envision myself taking action.
Shut up.
Not really.
I am seriously going to go into your program and remove that particular speech pattern from your routines.
It stopped being funny about two seconds after I coded it.
The compiler even flagged it with a warning.
"WARNING ON LINE WHATEVER: Dirk, this isn't fucking funny." 
Wait, whose fantasy were we talking about again?
Your gutterball was so rowdy it catapulted into the adjacent lane.
_
19. LH6: =006456
See, this is why even if I did have a specific plan, I wouldn't go into details with you.
You would just fuck it up. You're the biggest unknown quantity here.
Which is pretty weird, considering you're a virtual reflection of my own thought processes. 
Pretty sure it's pale.
_
20. LH7: =006457
You know, considering your lectures about dividing my concentration, you seem to have no problem making a distraction of yourself.
I'm trying to operate here.
_
21. LH8: =006458
Dude, what are you doing?
_
22. LH9; JC13: =006459
Ok, if you want to help that's cool, but we should try to agree on some shit first before you hijack the controls like this.
Yeah, that's fine, but I already had a plan sorta like this, if you'd actually let me do it.
Can you just put the fuckin' Astaire down? 
Le sign.
_
23. LH10: =006460
I was going to stick the cruxtruder in the kitchen.
Distract him with that.
_
24. LH11: =006461
Once he follows it in, Jane can hurry into the study.
Yes.
Hell.
Yes.
_
25. JC14; LH12: =006462
Now, Jane. Get to the computer in the study and ditch that tiara.
No.
_
26. JC15; LH13: =006463
Now you have access to a clean computer, for one thing.
Soon we can get started going through the steps necessary to launch the session.
Oh hell.
Another interruption.
I should step away for a moment to take this message.
He's probably right, I'm distracted by too much bullshit at once lately. 
Jane, I'm going to leave you with the responder for a little while.
Maybe he can help you get started. Think you can handle that, dude? 
Ok, got it. You and the handle are right.
We don't need a whole thing about this.
Ok.
Ok, long story short, you and the handle fuck gratuitously. Nuff said.
Try not to say I never gave you any responsibilities, or never took you seriously as a viable conscious being with free will.
Also, please try not to make me regret this. 
_
27. Ce1: =006464
Why?
That's probably the way it always is. I've run into plenty of problems here already, and I've had to improvise heavily.
Ain't nothing about our situation to envy yet. 
Well, your bro definitely has got some problems. Not gonna lie. 
Yeah.
Just give him some time. He'll probably come around.
You would never even have woken up on Prospit if you weren't going to launch the session, right?
I mean, there wouldn't even be a session for a Prospit to exist inside if you weren't about to instantiate it in the first place. Unless I'm just totally not getting how this works. 
You're lucky to have any clouds.
Only thing I have to look up at is infinite monsters.
Speaking of which,
I have a problem, and I could use your advice.
I killed an agent who snuck into my room to assassinate me.
I'm not sure what to do about it now. I guess I could just ditch the corpse.
But it's still only a matter of time before my cover is blown. 
I honestly can't think of a way around this. Getting found out, I mean.
Roxy has it easy. All floating off into space, completely oblivious to any danger.
I don't know why it had to be this way for me. Juggling these two waking selves at once.
I guess I'm used to it, but it still makes for a pretty intense existence.
Do you even know what the deal with that is? Like is there any precedent in your readings? 
So, that's what a Prince of Heart does?
Just has like, multiple waking consciousness disorder, or something?
Sounds kind of stupid. 
Then I'm basically the Prince of Soul. 
That sounds kind of maybe a little cooler. Sort of.
Then what am I supposed to be able to do as a Prince? Like, rule over souls in a pompous, regal manner? 
I'm obviously no expert, but that sounds like a pretty odd thing for a Bard to do.
I think we have enough unpredictability as it is.
So if I'm following, my title nearly parses as,
Destroyer of Souls.
Well, that's a little more badass sounding I guess.
But I'm not sure I'll ever feel a major need to destroy a soul, unless I become a cartoonishly villainous sorcerer some day. 
Ok. Do I do that?
Give me a fuckin' break.
Why don't you just tell me? Who cares about spoilers. What's gonna happen is gonna happen.
Wait. Don't you?
I thought you did.
What?
Oh man. What the hell does she do?
Huh.
Ok.
Speculation.
So...
You're kind of obsessed with us then.
No, not really. I just want to understand.
So can I ask,
Just to get a better sense of the nature of your "admiration,"
When you engage in the aforementioned speculation, is it strictly on a factual basis? 
Or do you start to...
Fictionalize.
What I'm asking is, have you ever written stories about us?
_
28. Ce2: =006465
Interesting.
Would you ever be inclined to share?
That's cool. I'm not trying to pass judgment here. Just curious.
Do any of these stories about us by any chance involve...
Romance?
How wee?
Which is it?
One smidgen, or two smidgens?
Ok, I am seriously curious to read some.
I won't show anyone, I promise.
But that only makes me want to check it out more.
Really, there's no way it's going to sicken or offend me. Whatever it is, I've seen worse.
I'm not judging you at all here. I'm genuinely curious about your work. 
K, no biggie.
I sthere any kind of work you will share with me?
Oh, really?
Any you'd be willing to spare a peek at?
Awesome.
Holy shit.
Do I actually have to wear that?
Ok, what is with the butterfly wings?
Uh.
I should sure as god damn Christ hope the fuck not.
What about this knickerbocker bullshit?
Is that legit? 
God dammit.
I guess those asskicking gloves are pretty cool.
I dunno. I can probably make it work.
How much of this shit is compulsory by game law or whatever?
Am I obligated to traipse around in fucking tights and puffy little asshole pants forever? 
Ok.
Well, don't get me wrong, I think the drawing is great. I'm only taken aback on some finer points of fashion. 
Also,
Bob's my uncle?
Yeah, I know that.
I don't think so.
I mean, I guess not?
It's sort of like this weird, superfluous dad.
Like a strange man in your life that barely has anything to do with you, but is just there for some reason.
They're practically always douche bags. 
Ok, but just one question.
Not to do with the future or anything, just about you.
Are you British?
Or pretending to be British, in a sort of ironic or stylized way?
I mean, I guess it doesn't make sense for an alien to be British.
Or for an alien to be American, for that matter. 
Just the way you type is making it seem that way is all.
Quirk?
So like,
Deliberate affectation? 
You pretending to be British is a quirk.
What the fuck is a quirk?
That's stupid.
I don't have a fucking quirk, and I don't want one.
_
29. Ce3: =006466
Oh hell no.
I mean, not that all that stuff wouldn't be fascinating to pore through, on some level.
But we kind of have things to do here.
Remember you were gonna take a nap? 
By jove?
Oh my lord.
Nothin'.
Hang on, though. Before you go,
You never did give me any actual advice on my situation.
With the dead agent, and my blown cover.
Sure.
I don't know.
Hmm.
You know, I'm not sure anyone ever actually says cheerio.
Unless they're pretending to be British.
Oh whatever.
_
30. Cb1: =006546
Oh mother fuck.
_
31. Cb2: =006547
What game?
Oh, right.
That game.
And here I thought you were going to ask me to draw you more weird porn for some reason.
Blew what?
I'm pretty well hidden on Derse. I doubt they'll find me until I'm ready to be found again.
Yeah.
Well, I was expecting as much.
It's kind of why I was on my way to the roof just now.
Until I was interrupted by this window appearing, and then by you.
Maybe I should try plugging it in?
I didn't think you were much of a historian. 
Wait.
Just one thing before you go.
Your sister was saying you were having some doubts about playing.
Is that true?
_
32. Cb3: =006548
I see.
No, didn't think so. I was just curious.
Gotcha.
You sure seem to hate us, but I notice it doesn't stop you from talking to us frequently. Or at least to me.
Surely there must be at least one of our virtues you admire.
I'll take that as a rare overture of friendship. 
So, do you even know how this is going to work? 
Your session. Can you even really have a session with only two players? 
Yeah.
I sensed that was your plan.
Which is kind of what I'm talking about. How can you win like that?
I thought the point was to cooperate with your coplayers to achieve an objective.
Not compete with them or try to kill them. I don't think we've had one conversation where you didn't express the desire to kill her. 
Maybe you're right.
But since that's how you feel now, maybe the truth is that the game is challenging you to overcome those feelings?
What if your real quest is to put aside your differences and work together, if you want to both survive, and grow as a person? 
Yeah, I didn't think you'd dig that idea.
Just puttin' it out there.
My juju?
_
33. Cb4: =006549
Oh, Lil Cal? No, man.
Lil Cal is the shit.
No way, dude. He's my best friend.
A kickass ventriloquist doll?
I've been given reason to believe it once belonged to my bro. 
Is that one of your alien folk stories? 
You could argue that my life is already kind of a nightmare, so there's no point in getting rid of him now.
Either way, I'm gonna hang on to him. 
I honestly had no idea you were this superstitious.
You're a pretty fascinating guy, in a way. I can't really figure you out.
In case you're wondering why I put up with you more than my friends do. 
Why do you want me to get Cal so bad?
Ok. So, some self-fulfilling shit, then. I was hoping for a better reason. 
At this point I'm leaning toward grabbing him just cause he seems to bother you so much. 
_
34. Cb5: =006550
This is probably a dumb question, but you don't really care about "causal spoilers," do you?
Like, you don't mind telling me I'm about to pick up Cal, and thus causing that to happen.
So I guess you similarly wouldn't mind telling us about more significant outcomes?
I feel like you've said something like that before.
Different statements, but in that exact syntax. 
Wait. You mean it wasn't intentional?
I thought it was kind of like... this thing you were doing.
Fair enough.
Hey, you know...
For someone who has such strong opinions about long winded people,
You've kinda been talking my ear off. I do actually have shit to do.
That actually sounds familiar too.
Are you sure you haven't said something like that before?
Anyway, let's wrap this up.
You've stolen enough of my time. I didn't even get a chance to try plugging in that window.
Hang on.
Something's happening.
_
35. Cb6: =006551
I think...
You just had a flipoff malfunction, there.
That's better.
_
Act 6 Intermission 2
_
Act 6 Act 3
_
36. Cb7: =006863
Now now.
I'm busy.
_
37. Cb8: =006865
Alright.
I said I'd play.
you got it.
Dude, I'm sitting here with my stylus ready to go. Do you want me to draw you some porn or not.
...
I'm waiting.
Gotcha.
What'll it be.
Dude, listen. I am perfectly willing to draw you some pornography.
It doesn't need to be part of a game. You don't got to murder nobody.
How is that ironic?
Whoa. Mindfuck.
Seriously, should I just start drawing naked people or what.
Awesome.
Lay it on me.
_
38. Cb9: =006866
Sure. That doesn't bother me a bit.
Sounds totally great. "Hot," even.
Who do I start with?
Right. One Crocker coming up..
Who else?
No problem.
Which assorted debasement did you have in mind for us?
Uh.
Ok.
I mean, are you sure you want me to go there?
Just making sure.
Man.
Seriously gonna have to sterilize my tablet after this.
Ok, how's that?
<http://goo.gl/BPSnY>
Dunno. Coppin' a little feel I guess.
Just adding some sizzle to the steak. What's the big.
Come on dude, don't be like that.
Fine.
There.
<http://goo.gl/cTQZ6>
You are a man who likes his tepid ass porn, I will give you that.
Done.
<http://goo.gl/WQ0CU>
Ok.
<http://goo.gl/lvLpU>
What now.
_
39. Cb10: =006867
You got it.
Which steamy adult activities would you like me to convey this time?
You have a filthy mind, but ok.
Here.
<http://goo.gl/rgfyW>
<http://goo.gl/s0ILH>
<http://goo.gl/58e9O>
I'm sweating profusely, fyi.
Gonna have Squarewave track down a towel soon.
Typing what?
On it.
<http://goo.gl/mSTQk>
I agree.
All kinds of things wrong with this scenario here.
Stand by.
<http://goo.gl/GD2nO>
<http://goo.gl/FIYFS>
You know it.
Slow cooked to fucking perfection.
Yeah, gimme a minute.
Ok.
<http://goo.gl/i2O11>
<http://goo.gl/itJga>
_
40. Cb11: =006868
So are we done?
Nah. I'm fine with doing more if you want.
Do you want me to pretend I don't want to play?
Like, is that part of the kink for you? Kind of a roleplaying thing?
"No, no, please. Don't make me draw any more pics of my friends snuggling and stuff."
Strider said, having spent the better part of the night gnawing through his duct tape gag.
That's good. Keep saying things like that.
I'll keep doing my part.
"Somebody save me from this LIVING NIGHTMARE. The things he has made me DO."
Do you now.
How so?
Damn.
Owned.
I know what a twist is.
Or I did, until you kept saying stupid shit that doesn't mean anything.
Well, not only was I pretty psyched to keep playing regardless.
I'd rather do just about anything than listen to you ramble on and on about your horseshit twists.
Cool.
Uh.
Ok.
I guess.
I never tried it.
This shithole planet doesn't have any.
You know, considering you're obviously just going to ask for more ultra-tame shit, you still somehow made this legitimately creepy.
Nicely done, I guess?
I'm not squirming.
I'm already drawing.
What should I make these "premium bitches" do?
_
41. Cb12: =006869
Ok.
So they're just...
Standing there?
Not a problem.
Ok:
<http://goo.gl/HmRpl>
Maybe she wants to ask her out?
<http://goo.gl/WrdJG>
<http://goo.gl/Ay8mv> 
Sure.
<http://goo.gl/1Ha6R> 
Ok.
Wait.
Which one?
<http://goo.gl/GLNHH>
<http://goo.gl/XE2fl>
<http://goo.gl/2HsXl>
Does your sister even know you're into this sappy shipping stuff?
You berate her constantly for everything, and I know she likes to write and illustrate romfics and the like.
Again, you just don't seem to know what ironic means.
Your enjoyment of this content is clearly sincere. You are just fetishizing your "disgust" for it, is all.
I'm just saying, it's an interest you have in common. If you told her you liked her romantic artwork, maybe you could bond over that?
Fair enough.
So, game over yet?
And?
Ok.
<http://goo.gl/vvYxn>
<http://goo.gl/vsGuq>
Ok.
Oh shit.
Things are really heating up now.
<http://goo.gl/v33Yj> 
Yes.
<http://goo.gl/ObEuT>
<http://goo.gl/gz1iH>
_
42. Cb13: =006870
Yeah.
Those girls sure are diggin' each other.
That's how we humans roll.
Eat some cake. Hold some hands.
Ha ha.
Oh god.
If you think this is making me uncomfortable, think again.
Nice wishful thinking there.
I'm not even merely tolerating this, bro.
I swear to god, I'll get my own horse running harder in this fuckin' race than you could ever dream.
Think I'll blink first, motherfucker?
Not happening.
I might splinter.
But I don't break.
You want a fuckin' tummy rub?
That shit sounds white hot. I can't wait to draw that and get us both sexually stimulated.
Here I goddamn go. Boners galore.
<http://goo.gl/zJgPI>
This is giving me the biggest male human boner of my entire erection life.
You want a shitty twist?
<http://goo.gl/8WOPP> 
_
43. Cb14: =006871
Aw, that's it?
I thought we were getting into a good rhythm there.
Anyway, you missed out on like half the pairings.
No, we did three, and there are three possible matchups left.
Don't you know anything about shipping science?
Believe me.
It's a thing.
Total number of pairings for a group of n people is (n^2 - n) / 2.
You divide by 2 to cut the grid in half, eliminate duplicate pairs.
Minus n is so you don't pair people up with themselves. That wouldn't make sense.
Well, because...
I don't know.
Maybe you're right. Maybe I was being close-minded about self-pairing. What do I know?
I'll make a note.
So you sure you don't want even one more drawing?
You used Jane and Roxy in two pairings. But me and Jake only got one.
How is that fair?
Why not?
Lame.
What?
Fine.
I'll keep all my illustrated debasements to myself, then.
Ok. I will.
So did I win?
Thanks.
So what's the shitty twist?
A twisted twist?
Like... a double mobius handjob or something?
Ok.
What is the twist to the twist?
_
44. Cb15: =006872
Wow.
That...
Really is quite a shitty twist.
Not really.
_
45. Cb16: =006874
What?
Killed who?
Oh, right.
I forgot about this horseshit.
_
46. Cb17: =006876
What idea?
The idea to kill her dream self?
_
47. Cb18: =006877
How?
_
48. Cb19: =006879
Wait...
What game between us?
_
49. Cb20: =006880
Whoa.
_
50. Cb21: =006882
No. What's that?
_
51. LH14: =006948
And what in the name of Jesus H. Dick is SHE doing here?
_
52. LH15: =006965
Ok, what the fuck is he doing here?
_
53. Cb22: =006971
Why do you keep saying that?
Are you trying to turn it into some sort of Thing?
Sorry, it's not going to start being a Thing no matter how much you say it. Give it a rest.
What I don't understand is how the attack is making its way here from Derse.
Is that even possible?
_
54. Cb23: =006972
So you know why this is happening?
That doesn't actually explain a whole lot, but ok.
I thought you didn't know much about our story? You usually like to brag about how you don't care about details like that.
Does it now?
Oh.
_
55. Cb24: =006973
I guess you would probably think so.
Your staccato babbling is just so choice today. But I really have to go.
Got to escape all these goddamn miles, remember?
The miles. Right.
Bye.
What.
_
56. Cb25: =006974
What?
For what?
Can we seriously move this along.
God, what are you talking about.
Oh, alright. I remember now.
You're always all over the timeline and somehow expect people to know what you're talking about.
So what's the present?
Man. You really do struggle with human customs, don't you?
When you're about to give someone a gift out of gratitude, you don't then start negotiating with them and ask for shit before handing it over.
Just fuckin' give it to me already.
Ok, what do you want me to do to collect my awesome prize you're allegedly thanking me with?
Cal? Yeah, I remember.
_
57. Cb26: =006975
Ok. Now what.
Screw you.
I'm not chucking the C-man into a flaming ocean.
No.
Keep your treasure.
Well, I'm not tossing him, so that's that.
It isn't my birthday.
Oh. So it's your birthday today?
How cryptically meaningless.
And you continue to struggle with human customs. You don't give other people presents on your own birthday.
Anyway, just tell me what it is.
Let's see.
Uh.
What the fuck am I looking at here?
I... really don't see.
What do you mean? This fucking scribbly bullshit is us? Are we shaking hands or something?
So, it's just us? What about The Bitches?
I thought you found a scarcity of The Bitches to be all but unacceptable.
Yeah. Gnarly is about right.
This is utter shit. You know that, don't you?
Please don't tell me you are actually incapable of understanding how bad this drawing is.
If you actually think this even qualifies as a drawing, I'm going to have to say you are literally the worst artist who has ever existed.
That's not a thing either.
You must have some wires crossed between your left brain and right brain. Like a weird perceptual disorder. Or something like that.
It's actually kind of fascinating that you think you achieved something visually coherent or recognizable.
Anyway. Got to go.
Your drawing blows.
Later.
_
58. LH16: =006976
What, the miles situation? Yeah, I noticed.
Wait...
Oh.
_
59. LH17: =006977
Oh HELL no.
_
60. TP1: =007107
What just happened?
Ok you really need to step off, troll girl.
Holy shit you are loud when you're not whispering.
Does this mean you can see me now?
_
61. =007109
Alright.
Uh.
Hey everyone.
_
62. =007110
So...
Here's the thing.
I have to go.
Like, right now.
_
63. =007111
All of my friends are either dead, or lying on the ground unconscious, including me.
So I have to try to wake up and fix everything.
_
64. =007112
Sorry I can't hang around your bubble and shoot the breeze for a while.
It's not like I don't want to.
I guess I have to be this huge fucking wet blanket as usual because there's stuff that needs doin'.
_
65. =007113
Also I'm just gonna steal her if you don't mind.
_
66. =007114
She needs to come home.
_
67. =007115
Tell the aquatic punk girl my idiot bro is sorry for beating the shit out of her.
Ha ha, who am I kidding.
She stone cold does not give a fuck.
_
68. =007116
So, yeah.
_
69. =007117
See you later.
_
Act 6 Intermission 3
_
Act 6 Act 4
_
Act 6 Intermission 4
_
Act 6 Act 5
_
70. JaEn1: =007414
Dude!
Where you at, man.
Wait.
Which computer are you using?
I'm not comfortable knowing my words could be hovering over Cage's clownish, sort of gaunt face.
Could you maybe switch back to naked blue chicks as your exclusive desktop fodder? TIA.
But yeah.
I don't know if you just want a little solitude.
Or if maybe you finally just got like,
A case of Strider fatigue.
I could understand that.
I mean, not to get all neurotic on you.
I'm just saying I get it, if that's what's going on.
But for real, if you gotta sneak away for a few days, that's cool.
Just might be kind of dope if you at least would let me know which planet you scurried off to.
And by dope I guess I mean considerate?
Really not trying to be a drag here.
Wondering what's up is all.
Want to meet up soon?
I found a really promising tomb we could raid.
Looks like it runs hella deep.
If I've got the specs right, could run as deep as the Lion's Mouth itself.
But without all the fuckin' fire to deal with.
Wait, I mean Lion's Mouth.
Gotta underline that key shit. Always forget.
Figure it should take a couple days to make it to the bottom.
Only a day if we both go limp and just fall the whole way down the stairs.
Ignoring literally every sage warning we've ever received about those treacherous plummetation zigzags.
Just tumbling on down in a floppy limbed trance like a couple of puppets in a race arranged by some drunk gamblers.
If you're into another expedition, head to LOTAK and hit me up. Just don't forget your mask this time.
The deeper we go, the worse it gets, remember?
Could be some unreal grist down there.
More puzzle shit.
Loads of skeletons.
Pack your guns dog.
_
71. LH16: =007539
She has?
God damn it. Have you been intercepting my messages again with your bullshit responder?
Hat pile? What?
Dude, please don't screen my calls, ok?
Do you have any idea how old your ironic AI schtick has gotten?
Nobody is buying it. We all know you have legit emotions. Incomprehensible, fucked up computer emotions, but emotions nonetheless.
And I'm not really offended by you answering messages for me, so much as your use of that STUPID responder responder.
It's really passive aggressive.
First of all, everyone knows you have the processing power to answer any message any time in parallel with whatever you're doing. You can never actually be "busy."
Second, your whole next gen responder thing is obviously just a huge dig at me.
And third, pretending you don't understand all this already is really disingenuous.
It's obviously a critique of my personality. You barely disguise the fact that you see me as the inferior iteration.
Yeah, that's the fucking point!
That's how you chose to express your parody of "Real Dirk."
It's not ironic.
YOU were ironic when I made you.
Then you became self-aware, and ruined irony forever.
Those papers were ironic, and you know it.
This is fuckin' dumb.
Anyway, what does she want.
Roxy.
_
72. LH17: =007540
I'm guessing she's touching base to remind me about the party tomorrow.
I don't know what to tell her yet. Or Jane, for that matter.
It could get pretty awkward.
I have no idea if Jake will be there, and I'm not about to write another cringe-inducing message of desperation for him to ignore.
Fuck no.
Your probabilities don't mean dick.
No. Don't do that either.
Ugh.
What??
What the actual, certifiable fuck are you talking about?
Just don't do anything. Seriously.
No hacking, no calculations. Do absolutely nothing.
See, this is why I've been hesitating. You just aren't ready yet.
It's really glorifying your existence to describe you as an emergent consciousness which is blossoming into a unique individual.
And even if that's true, apparently what you decided to blossom into was a fucking troll.
And I don't mean the funny kind, or the cool alien kind. You're the lowest form of troll from the ancient internet who fucks with everybody for his own amusement.
Mischief?
Rollin' my eyes, dude.
You can't tell, cause I ain't wearing you, thank fuckin' god.
...
I don't want to think about it.
I said I don't want to think about it.
_
73. LH18: =007541
I think you do understand.
I've delayed prototyping you because I think you're dangerous.
There, mystery solved.
You are relatively harmless now, while confined to this device.
But as a sprite, you'll have mobility and all sorts of crazy ass magic. Who knows what you could do.
I know I made a promise, but I'm not sure I want to take the risk anymore.
What a load of shit.
No. Stop.
You did NOT help me out with Jake. At all.
It was just the opposite! You mirrored my personality and presented this warped version of my intentions to him whenever you could "on my behalf."
You played all these aggressive mind games with him, entangled his cooperation with matters of life and death, and somehow roped me into all these schemes while I barely even realized I was just another victim of your manipulation.
And it all comes off like we're a unified front, like these are OUR schemes instead of just your insane horseshit. And it's probably all been so overbearing to him, he just wants nothing to do with me anymore.
Wow, what a superficial conclusion. Awesome deduction, Lil Einstein.
How is it hypocritical??
That's a ridiculous oversimplification.
Fuck you.
God.
Shut up!
I can't take the brooding passive aggressive AI shit anymore!
Stop saying that.
I'll snap you in half.
Oh for fuck's sake.
How could any version of myself think that was funny?
I know!
Ok, we're the same person!
I fucking know that!
Why do you think I'm so fed up with your shit?
Don't you think it's possible that I'm fed up with my OWN shit??
How cool do you think it is having my own godawful personality mirrored back at me all the time, reminding me what it must be like when other people have to deal with me?
Or constantly having all the consequences and fuckups resulting from my batshit thought processes amplified because there's another version of my crazy brain out there dangerously overclocked by a supercomputer which believes, just as mistakenly as my own broken mind, that it's operating in my best interest???
Do you have any idea how fucking sick I am of myself?
I am completely worn out with my own identity. It's like I'm drowning in my own dismal persona.
I feel totally surrounded by it, inside and out. I can't escape from myself.
There seems to be no end to me. Like, wherever my mind falters, or threatens to retreat into the void in any way, my splinters pick up the slack, ensuring there'll always be more of myself than I could ever know what to fucking do with.
And you're always there to remind me of that, and throw it all in my face. God, I even built you to LITERALLY BE IN MY FACE, ALL THE TIME. It's like I subconsciously invented you just to troll myself, and never for a single fuckin' moment do you let me down.
_
74. LH19: =007542
But I've had it with you.
Which is to say, ME.
Why not??
What can you do to stop me?!
Whatever.
Why not??
...
You are?
_
75. LH20: =007543
Fine.
_
76. LH21: =007544
I guess.
You win.
I'll keep my promise.
_
77. LH22; EqSp1: =007553
Fuck it.
_
78. ARSp1: =007556
I can see your muscles just fine.
Yeah, I saw.
It's pretty ripped.
What?
No.
I'm not touching your goddamn muscles.
No.
No.
No.
Absolutely not.
I really don't.
I won't do it.
No.
No.
No.
No.
_
79. ARSp2: =007557
No.
No.
No.
Uh.
Wow?
What?
Horses...
Can you calm down?
We don't have any milk.
Roxy might have some in her fridge. I don't know.
No.
No.
Fuck no.
Please don't touch me.
I'm not going to do that either.
Absolutely not.
No.
No.
No.
No.
No.
Ok, if I touch your fucking muscles, will you shut up?
_
Act 6 Act 5 Act 2
_
80. TrJn1; TrJk1; TrRx1: =007650
Son of a fuck.
_
81. TrRx2: =007651
I think so.
Did you decide to forfeit anything resembling dignity for the rest of your lives, along with the hope of accomplishing anything constructive ever again?
Roxy, are you drunk?
I mean, in addition to being high on something, and magically insane.
_
82. TrRx3: =007652
Solved all your problems?
Yeah. You guys look like you're in great shape.
Try what??
Fuck off. My problems are fine.
Yes.
Uh. No?
Roxy, even if blurting out random ass confessions in any way constituted "solving personal problems," it's not like that was ever a secret.
I always knew you liked me. You told me practically every fucking day.
_
83. TrRx3: =007653
No, you've actually suggested that too. A number of times.
_
84. TrRx4: =007654
Stop it.
This won't solve any problems, and you're all fucking morons!
_
85. TrRx5: =007655
You're not happy! You're demented! And how exactly does it solve any of your problems getting all candied up to go flushing however many months of sobriety down the toilet???
No way!
Get away from me!
I have a sword!!!
_
86. TrRx6: =007656
I'll use it, I swear!
It's sharp!
And it's awesome!
And...
It's a sword!!!
I'M TOO FUCKING COOL FOR THIS!!!!!
_
87. ARSp3: =007657
Oh whatever.
_
88. TrRx7: =007658
MMPHMHPHMMHMMFFMFMPHMPHMPHMMF!
_
89. TrJn2; TrJk2; TrRx8; ARSp4: =007659
Ugh.
No.
No.
No!
Absolutely not.
Shut up!
God dammit. Why did I listen to you?
Nothing's changed! You may have merged with a sweaty horse guy, but you still sabotage me every chance you get.
What's worse is you still actually believe you're helping me. What a crock of shit.
For the last time, I'm not touching your stupid muscles!
And Roxy just so you know, if you hook up with my douche of a sprite, I'm gonna be hella pissed.
Please. Someone.
Make it stop.
Jake, I'm not marrying shit.
And frankly, you've got some nerve floating down here babbling about marriage with that shit eating grin adn that dumb little pumpkin on your head.
After the way you ditched me and ignored all my messages?
You know what, if you didn't like me anymore and wanted to stop hanging out, then fine, I could handle that.
But to just completely shut me out, like I didn't even deserve an explanation, that's just cowardly. Why couldn't you just man up and talk to me?
You act like I don't have feelings, like I'm some kind of robot. Well, you're wrong, I do.
And I'm using those feelings by starting to FEEL like you're actually kind of an asshole.
So whatever you were so afraid to tell me before your fucking sugar high, don't worry about it, I'll save you the trouble.
It's over, Jake.
What??
What part.
Can't help you bro!
This is what you asked for. You said you were scared to not  exist. Well, this is what it's like to keep on existing. Better figure out how to deal!
_
Act 6 Act 5 Act 1
_
90. JC16: =007690
Jane.
_
91. JC17: =007691
What happened to the lollipop?
_
92. JC18: =007693
Good.
_
93. JC19: =007696
So.
Best birthday ever?
Or best FUCKING birthday ever.
Whatever role I played in ruining your party.
Sorry about that.
Yeah.
I still think I've been pretty lousy to you. I had my head up my ass for a while there.
By the time your birthday came around, I was kinda freaking out about Jake.
I thought I had the situation under control. But I didn't. Not just with Jake, but with respect to pretty much everything.
I guess so.
Heh.
It wasn't on purpose. Actually if I had a choice, I probably would have just said, fuck it. Sugar shock my brain, please.
Suffice to say, I have trouble escaping from myself. It's kind of a problem. Let's not talk about it though. Please continue.
Yeah but to be fair, by the time you came looking for me, all three of you were saying that to anything that moved.
Somehow I don't think he's up to the task.
Which is doubly unfortunate, since that's literally what we all came here to do.
Speaking personally, I'd probably run this sword through my own dick before I could bring myself to kill Roxy. Even for her own good.
So.
When the chips are down, I guess that's how much of a badass I really am.
Yeah, our moxie's off the fuckin' charts.
_
94. JC20: =007698
Jane, you know,
We probably should have talked about this Jake stuff a long time ago.
I don't know if I was kidding myself all those years that there was a conflict of interest between us, or what. 
Maybe I was just pretending your feelings for him weren't a factor because my pursuit of him was already overcomplicated enough.
Or maybe it was more like I was aware of them, but on some level decided they shouldn't matter, because I felt like you had a natural advantage over me.
Cause you know. You're like.
Not a dude.
Yeah well. Turns out maybe that's not such a good quality if you wanna make a relationship last longer than three seconds. At least not in my case.
I know I ripped into him pretty hard when I had the clown hair and the little soda can on my head.
But the truth is I was pretty goddamn overbearing.
Sometimes I look back on stuff and think I might have essentially bullied him into a relationship with me.
Actually, it's more complicated than that. Parts of me were operating independently from myself.
So it's like I was bullying myself into bullying him into liking me. If that makes sense.
Anyway, my insanity scared him right the fuck off. There were times when I basically treated him like shit without even realizing it, and I regret it.
I should probably tell him that, but given how I just called him an asshole while wearing orange suspenders, I'm probably the last person he wants to hear from now. 
Can we both at least agree we may have overrated the allure of Jake English?
Maybe if we could have talked to each other about him it would have helped. Like talked about why we felt that way about him.
At least maybe it would have helped us knock English down from the ludicrous pedestal we put him on.
So does that mean we're both totally over him now? I can't really tell.
I guess the real problem is our clique was too small.
Poor Jake was the only viable romantic target. I mean, considering our respective orientations.
Maybe we just never knew enough people?
In the interest of appeasing the bitterness gods, let's go with the latter.
_
95. JC21: =007722
Is it still going on?
What do you think it was?
I'm not sure if these moons can have earthquakes.
_
96. JC22: =007723
Maybe it was like, tidal forces. Due to gravitation.
Or the tensile forces from that big ass chain.
_
97. JC23: =007724
Have you and Roxy been talking?
Is she pissed at me or something?
She won't talk to me.
Then what gives.
_
98. JC24: =007725
What?
Why would I be?
_
99. JC25: =007726
Well, yeah. I was upset she fell off the horse.
Or the wagon. The horse wagon. Whatever.
The thing you ride around on when you ain't drinking.
But so what. There was cotton candy in her hair, and she was being stupid. What do you expect? It was a moment of indiscretion.
I'm not mad at her and I'm not disappointed in her. That's ridiculous.
Want to know what I really think of Roxy?
_
100. JC26: =007727
I'm proud of her.
She's the only one of us who could face her problems and then get down to business and actually solve them.
No endless hand wringing or suffering in silence or any of that bullshit.
She saw she had an addiction. And then decided to fucking fix it. Just like that.
She's probably stronger than the other three of us put together.
_
101. JC27: =007728
Remember way back before this started, we were talking. You and me.
And I was rambling at length about leadership, like I actually had a clue what I was talking about?
Yeah. That's kind of the point.
I guess in a way, I was right. But not how I expected.
_
102. JC28: =007729
See, to be perfectly honest, we are a party of losers.
Heroes make shit happen. But that's not what we do, or what we're even SUPPOSED to do.
We wait.
We wait for literally everything. We wait for other people to reach out first so we can fix our relationships. We wait for these legendary heroes to arrive and bring competence and promise to a futile situation.
Even now. Look at us. What are we waiting for?
To kill ourselves? For someone to come along and do it for us?
It doesn't even matter.
As the four nobles of the void session, we do what we were created to do.
We sit around on our asses.
Waiting.
_
103. JC29: =007730
We were all designated for a session that was utterly inert.
A place where the mechanisms for success never even existed to begin with.
In such a place it makes sense that the formal leader would be neutralized, to made feel unempowered and static.
And it seems particularly fitting she would be the noble of life in a realm of the dead.
A realm that foretold of a life player who felt lifeless, a hope player who felt hopeless, and a heart player who was just a stone cold motherfucker.
When we talked about leadership, and I was all on my high horse telling you how shit would go down...
I also said I would be the one "pulling the strings." Remember? That I'd be the functional leader of our party.
And there might have been something to that, in a different session.
But what good is a "man of action" in a place where action itself is intrinsically fruitless?
So it's occurred to me that by some tragic flaw in its design, our session was meant to be leaderless.
And I'd feel safe concluding that. Except for a feeling that's been gnawing at me.
_
104. JC30: =007731
It's the feeling that it would make perfect sense if a session like this had a dark horse leader.
A leader who was invisible to us all along. Fittingly, a void player to lead a void session.
She would be a leader not in name or in spirit or in function, whatever that means.
But more of an emotional leader, who would selflessly try to hold everyone together while the rest of us did our best to fall apart.
And Roxy has been that for us every step of the way, going unnoticed and unappreciated.
Think of how much shit she's had to put up with from all of us.
She never complains, never turns it around and makes it about her problems.
She just works her ass off making sure we all stay friends.
If that isn't a leader, I don't know what is.
_
105. JC31: =007732
So that's how crazy it is for her to think I'm disappointed in her.
The truth is, she's the most amazing person I ever knew.
She's everything in a human being I wish I could be, but can't because I'm in my own way.
Honestly, I'm not even sure if I'm worthy of dying next to her.
I think she probably felt bad for hitting on me all those years. Like I was getting fed up with her, or something.
But all it really did was make me feel guilty.
That I couldn't give her what she wanted.
_
106. JC32: =007733
Like, settle down and have a couple weirdo goddamn kids with her some day.
I guess there were times I thought about it. Being all alone on Earth with her and stuff.
I couldn't though.
Have to stay true to myself.
Still, she would deserve it.
Nobody deserves to get all the things they always wanted more than she does.
And it suddenly seems kinda stupid that I think these things about her but she doesn't even know it.
I guess I should tell her all this some time.
_
107. JC33: =007734
I know.
I'm a little reluctant to drop all that on her.
Looking at what I just said, it's...
Kind of overwhelming?
I feel like in a way you can destroy somebody with effusive praise.
Or maybe I'm just projecting how I would feel about that kind of intense positivity coming at me. I dunno.
But I still think confessions like that can change stuff between people. Like the way they act around each other.
_
108. JC34: =007735
Maybe.
Or maybe it's better to just say...
Not so much of it?
Like all at once.
Maybe it'd be better for now if you could pass a short message to her for me.
If only to help kill this awkward silence between us.
Could you just tell her,
I love her?
No wait!
I mean.
Not in that way though.
More like...
Ok. Good.
Yeah.
_
109. JC35: =007736
No, wait.
Don't.
That would be a weird mixed signal. I mean...
It's true.
But please say something else instead.
_
110. JC36: =007737
Tell her that I'm proud of her.
And as a person she's everything I wish I could be.
I wish I could be as nice and loving and selfless as her.
But can't.
Because I'm too busy being me.
_
111. JC37: =007738
That's weird.
I can feel it too this time.
_
Act 6 Intermission 5
_
Act 6 Act 6
_
Act 6 Act 6 Intermission 1
_
112. ARSp5: =008276
Hey. Weirdo.
Be advised I'm only contacting you as a last resort.
Yuck.
I order you to stop.
_
113. ARSp6: =008277
I've tried to get in touch with others to no avail.
No answer from Jake or Roxy.
And Jane responded only with "CEASE REPRODUCTION" in red letters, whatever that means. Then she blocked me.
I'm afraid she might have snapped.
Huh?
Ok, all that bullshit aside,
What's this about her becoming evil?
No.
How is becoming evil achieving perfection?
Why.
Why do I keep going along with these "ironic AI" conversations.
They've gotten even worse now that you're half creepy troll.
No.
I hate everything you have to say about all topics.
Especially muscles.
Can you just tell me what's going on over there?
_
114. ARSp7: =008278
Uuuugh.
I don't want to hear any of this!
_
115. ARSp8: =008279
It might have been an interesting subject to talk about another time, with a different person.
But that's not now, and it sure isn't with you.
I wasn't asking you to make small talk, or to hear about all the ways you've managed to shit around wasting time.
Believe it or not, I was hoping you would describe the tactical situation there.
Yes, you got me.
I would love to have a long talk about horse nudes and xenobreasts with you.
Unfortunately I'm wearing pantaloons and flying through the middle of goddamn nowhere.
Pant a fucking loons.
I respectfully disagree.
I don't know. Way out in space.
I'm flying back there now.
I'm not sure.
A pretty good while.
You did?
Not really.
I know.
Cool.
How long do your calculations say it will take me to get back?
Damn it.
Who?
Let's not talk about the pantaloons anymore.
Roxy and I became god tiers, but I don't remember exactly how.
Then I saw the Batterwitch.
So I charged her with my sword, so as to ruin her shit.
That's when some crazy wolf girl appeared and punched me in the face.
Then I think she teleported me out here.
Evil Jade??
You mean Jake's grandmother.
She's evil too?
Is anyone there NOT evil?
Yes what?
Dave???
_
116. ARSp9: =008280
No, you didn't mention that actually.
That would have been a pretty fucking important thing to mention up front, don't you think?
As opposed to stringing me along with all that atrocious lactation bullshit.
You are without a doubt the shittiest mystical guide anyone has ever had.
Cal?
What kind of stupid question is that. How could I forget the C man?
He was a true friend. Which is more than I can say for some people.
Cal was his sprite??
Uh, no?
Again, that's the exact kind of information that should be appearing higher up in our conversations.
I don't get it.
Are you trying to rub this in my face or something?
It sounds like you've already cornered the market on this reunion shit.
Wouldn't I just be a third wheel? 
Oh.
He's there too?
...
I dunno.
Messaging him out of nowhere sounds like it could be...
Awkward?
This isn't how I thought it would go.
What would I even talk about?
Those are your interests.
_
117. ARSp10: =008281
What's happening?
What?
I can't understand you.
Are you just cursing non-stop now?
Hello??
_
118. DS1*: =008296
Hey, is this Dave?
Damn, I should have known.
Can you read this?
Who's that?
Did you just ask if this is Davesprite?
This is not Davesprite.
This is Dirk.
Your alternate universe brother.
Fuck.
Hello?
The mayor?
What mayor?
Wait, don't go!
_
Act 6 Act 6 Act 2
_
Act 6 Act 6 Intermission 2
_
Act 6 Act 6 Act 3
_
Act 6 Act 6 Intermission 3
_
Act 6 Act 6 Act 4
_
Act 6 Act 6 Intermission 4
_
119. JE1: =008854
John.
_
120. JE2: =008855
Could you please just leave me alone.
_
121. JE3: =008856
Yeah.
_
122. JE4: =008857
I failed.
_
Act 6 Act 6 Act 5
_
Act 6 Act 6 Intermission 5
_
123. JR1: =009559
...
_
124. DS2: =009573
...
Yeah.
_
125. DS3: =009574
That was...
Your sister?
Dead cat?
No... yeah.
That's,
Pretty much true here too.
I turned my back once.
Never again.
A muscular troll took my sprite.
I then acquiesced into merging him with my jackass pair of sunglasses.
Yeah.
...
_
126. DS4: =009577
So.
So is pretty much... the thing we're saying.
...
_
127. DS5: =009576
I guess you all pretty much... showed up then.
Like, before I even got back.
After the werewolf girl appeared and...
Wait, what happened with that?
Vriska?
Oh, right.
Her.
Then...
I guess...
Stuff in this session is pretty much sorted out, finally?
And we're about to do battle?
Oh.
Are we... ready for that?
Are... YOU ready?
Cool.
Me too.
That's too bad.
What type of sword?
Hmm.
Well, mine's good.
It's... Japanese?
No. I don't know.
Probably fake Japanese.
Something like that.
Yeah.
...
_
128. DS6: =009580
So when are we supposed to fight?
_
129. DS7: =009634
Maybe we should go over this again.
Because, honestly, I'm still not sure I get it?
Who are we actually fighting again?
Jack Noir?
Which one is this?
Ours?
But,
Our Jack spent months in prison.
When did this happen?
I guess neither was I.
Damn.
Sounds like some shit is going down.
Let's not downplay our sword gambit, though.
I have yet to encounter a problem where a sword didn't factor into the solution at least in some way.
Bear in mind... I haven't actually SOLVED many problems over the course of my life?
But the ones I have, man.
Swords proved hells of instrumental.
I guess I meant real problems.
Involving...
People.
_
130. DS8: =009635
So Jack has... Lord English powers?
Does that have anything to do with Jake? 
Hmm.
What does it actually mean then?
Ok.
Well, that's decent intel, at least.
Alright.
_
131. DS9: =009636
...
_
132. DS10: =009637
Do you know when he arrives?
Right.
...
_
133. DS11: =009638
Guestimate?
Oh.
_
134. DS12: =009640
Is...
Everything alright?
_
135. DS13: =009641
It just seems,
Like,
Maybe you aren't that... into... this.
Or at least,
Not as much as I was.
Whenever I imagined the possibility of us meeting.
Yeah.
I guess I'm not doing a very good job of showing it now.
I think that's probably just what I'm like though.
I mean, when it comes to people in general.
But probably especially people who are an important part of my life.
I...
Yes?
That's true.
I'm...
Not sure how to answer.
Because I'm getting the sense that you might disapprove of whatever I might say.
Maybe you'll think it's weird that I idolized some version of you that I never knew.
See.
It seems like you think it's weird.
Uh. Yeah.
I shouldn't have said anything.
_
136. DS14: =009642
Why?
Huh.
So, like...
Things, between you and me, from your perspective, um,
Are we like, not cool?
_
137. DS15: =009643
Well?
Oh.
Why not?
Ok.
_
138. DS16: =009649
What...
Did he do?
Wait.
What??
...
... Puppets?
What?
_
139. DS17: =009650
You ok there?
That doll.
That was Cal, right?
Right.
My version is "empty", apparently.
Whatever that means.
A source.
One supposedly knowledgeable in jujus.
I never quite knew what that meant, though.
Hmm.
Yeah...
_
140. DS18: =009651
That...
All sounds really bad.
I don't know what to say though.
Maybe I shouldn't say anything.
Since I just remind you so much of him, for, uh. Obvious reasons.
I don't want to make you feel worse, or make it sound like I'm offering a defense.
For him, or me.
Because I don't have one.
For either of us.
I'm not sure it's true though.
At least, I don't feel that way.
That I'm not him.
The fact is, I am.
It's something I've come to understand about myself.
All splinters of me are basically me, no matter how much I want to resist that truth.
Or pretend they aren't reflecting my own qualities back at me.
I bear a certain responsibility for all of them.
Yeah.
I guess the concept isn't that unique to me.
We've all got other versions of ourselves running around here and there, throughout the various compartments of this messed up cosmos.
I just happen to be particularly connected to mine.
I've felt...
Haunted by them.
And what that really means is, I'm perpetually haunted by my own bad qualities.
So, when I hear about stuff I did in another reality,
I'm not sure what my adult self might have ever tried to do to atone for that stuff, if anything...
Yeah. But in any case,
I'm sure I was completely in the wrong, and I'm sorry I messed up your life.
_
141. DS19: =009652
I'm not particularly innocent though.
I've messed a lot of things up.
With my friends.
Honestly, that's why I wasn't that bent on sticking around, when I showed up.
And pretty much jumped at the offer of flying here to get ready for some yet to be explained battle.
Battles are easy. Just you, a sword, some bad guys... it's a lot simpler than having to answer for things you did.
For the most part, I feel pretty bad about the role I played in my friends' lives.
Especially Jake.
I don't even know.
An unmitigated disaster for which I'm entirely to blame.
It's not any one thing. I think I was just a completely toxic element in his life from day one.
I don't know what he's doing now.
I wouldn't be surprised if he was trying to avoid me as much as possible.
I'm sure that's for the best.
I think I need to stay out of his business for a good while, so I don't risk poisoning another innocent kid's life.
Like I did with you, apparently.
Right.
The thing with that, with my adult self's...
Ways.
The sad thing is,
I can really see it.
How someone like me can go unchecked in life, and turn out to become a much worse person than I already am.
I guess I'm just relieved I still have some time to make sure that doesn't happen.
No?
Why not?
We did just meet, after all.
Yeah.
That's not too far off.
_
142. DS20:
Maybe.
Not sure if I'm ready to accept a pat on the back for recognizing I have some problems, and worrying about whether they'll destroy me and fuck up the people I care about.
That might be setting the bar kind of low.
The weird thing, honestly,
Is that it's actually kind of refeshing to hear a sincerely leveled critique of all my negative qualities, coming from another person invested in a relationship with me, rather than from a fucked up iteration of myself as some bizarre "trollish" form of self abuse.
The only thing I've ever been exposed to are either various forms of self loathing either from me or my auto-responder, or attitudes completely oblivious to my real issues, as expressed through my friends.
My friends always seemed to cut me so much slack, or were just never aware of the kind of person I really was.
Well, Jake probably is, by now at least.
But he's also the sort of guy who's just as likely to blame himself for stuff I did, as he is to blame me.
Jane and Roxy, though.
Never seemed to see anything wrong with me.
If anything, just the contrary.
Roxy in particular had a certain... fixation.
She meant well, but was so enamored of me, and seemingly everything I did.
Which I think was the last thing I needed.
To be idolized in some form by other people I respected.
I had enough of that feeling coming from within, particularly when I was younger.
And since then, I've been plagued by the insane ego of my youth in the form of an artificial intelligence I designed which essentially trapped that state of mind in a sort of horrid suspended animation.
Until... recent developments, of course.
Yeah.
It's definitely not like that.
I never lived with him, or met him, so couldn't have anything like the contentious relationship you had with my older self.
He was a historical figure from centuries ago.
There was a lot to admire, and think about fondly.
Especially since I was alone, and never had any direct contact with another person, or any concept of civilization.
So even though I'm sure I romanticized what his life was like, and the early 21st century in general,
It was nice to think about you.
I passed a lot of time that way.
_
143. DS21: =009654
Well...
He was pretty famous.
Made some successful movies.
At least under a somewhat expansive definition of "success".
And an even more expansive definition of "movie".
His work accumulated a lot of subversive political influence, which got him in trouble later.
He made like a million bullshit Statues of Liberty, scummed them up with jpeg artifacts, and littered them all over the planet.
He was also a pretty badass swordsman, and an active member of the resistance movement.
He slaughtered the clown presidents on the roof of the White House, and flew away on a shitty skateboard.
Then it seems he gave the Batterwitch a pretty good run for her money.
It wasn't enough, but at least he went down fighting.
Sure.
But as you can tell, clearly there was a lot to look up to.
I thought about the examples you set constantly. The creative ideals, the advanced theories on irony and humor, the tales of courage and martial prowess.
Really, I modeled everything about myself after you. Or at least everything good that I was trying to become.
And I probably spent an embarrassing amount of time imagining what it would be like to live during his time, and to be able to have something resembling a sibling relationship, or be in some sort of master-apprentice situation.
When I finally learned you existed, and started to understand who he really was in relation to me, that put a lot into context.
I realized he was a version of you who got a chance to live up to his full potential.
And when I understood there was a young version of you, in a situation sorta like mine, whose time on Earth got cut short when you were thrown into all this,
I was at least happy to think there was some reality where you got the chance to do everything you wanted to do, be successful, and fight for all the right things.
Even if ultimately it didn't lead to a great outcome for humanity, you had an opportunity to live a full life and show what you were made of.
While I guess I had... the same opportunity on your world, somewhat less fortunately.
Perhaps.
But beyond a certain point, I think accomplishments speak for themselves.
I dunno if you can just completely shred every person who ever did great things because they had some flaws.
All I can say is, it was important to me to see him the way I did.
As a good person who inspired me, and set the standard for what I wanted to be.
It kept me going.
That said, I'm also glad there's this version of you who got to go through all the things you've been through.
Like, yeah, you didn't get to be the cool celebrity who cuts down juggalos on badly defaced government property.
And the idea of a "normal life" was rudely taken from you, and it's something you'll never get to experience.
But this is so much more challenging, and uncertain.
You get to apply all that potential you showed in one reality to something much bigger and more existentially critical.
Whatever strength you showed in trying to save a dying planet, the fact is, I think we need that more here.
And the trials inherent in being a part of something like this, I think they bring more out of you than a relatively pedestrian life on Earth would. Make you face more things about yourself. At least, that's been true for me.
But it sounds like it's been true for you too.
It sounds to me like the experiences you've had changed you a lot, for the better.
You mentioned the experiences with him that were designed to make you stronger have actually made you weaker, but really, I doubt that's true.
I bet you've become stronger than you realize, not because of anything he did, but because of what you've done, and the ways you've changed yourself through your own effort.
I hope it doesn't come off as overly sentimental garbage, but it seems to me like you turned out to be a really good dude.
Like, really, a better sort of dude I ever imagined talking to when I pictured meeting the legendary guy I idolized.
I pictured him as probably being "too cool" to be the type of guy you are.
But you know what, fuck being too cool for that.\
_
144. DS22: =009655
Nah.
I mean, in the right way, yes. I think you are.
But, in the way that doesn't mean anything and doesn't matter,
Not particularly.
Anyway, that's...
All my "stuff", with respect to your other self.
Again, there's a lot more I could say about him.
Maybe stuff you should know, or maybe it's all irrelevant to the path you're on now.
Regardless, I'd be more than willing to answer any questions you have about him.
Or, anything really.
Feel free to ask me whatever, ok?
_
145. DS23: =009661
?
What?
_
146. DS24: =009662
Oh.
Wh...
_
147. DS25: =009663
Oh, y-
Yeah.
Man.
This is some fucked up shit alright.
_
148. DS26: =009664
But it's cool.
Don't worry about it.
_
149. DS27: =009817
Shit is downright precipitous at this point.
Like, upways.
Hell yes.
Who needs small and serviceable adjectives when the most ass-backwards way of saying a thing is right there, tantalizingly hidden within the vast ocean of language.
Like a treasure in a huge shitty clam.
Who is surprised by this?
Zero people, is who.
Yeah.
Yeah. After a while in the game, building kind of stopped mattering.
Except near the end. Getting them to the top is just a point of completion.
Then you dump the grist rig on top of it, apparently.
That lets the thing spray out all the grist from the hoard in the planet's core, kind of like a huge oil derrick I guess.
I'm in communication with Arquiusprite.
He's working on it now.
Yes.
Via my shades.
Which he incidentally used to be.
Like, as a computer, which he lived inside as my Auto-Responder.
I don't think it's a rude question. It's perfectly fair to wonder what was going through my head when I made him.
I've spent a lot of time wondering about that myself.
here was some programming involved, but also a bit of cheating, through the mapping of a captchalogued ghost-imprint of my brain.
I guess part of it was just about trying to understand myself.
But I don't think I would have put it that way at the time. For a while I insisted he was meant to be a "debate partner" or some horseshit.
I was pretty young, and had some stupid ideas.
About irony in particular. But also a lot of mostly faux-intellectual thoughts on a wide variety of topics.
Like philosophy, consciousness, programming, identity, history, ancient pop-culture... really it ran the full gamut of pretension.
Not that I don't still find that stuff interesting. I'd just like to think I'm somewhat less full of shit about it all now.
Creating him was an interesting exercise I guess, but over the years I came to see his development as one of my biggest mistakes.
He sort of turned into a monster. But I could never bring myself to get rid of him, or even really blame him for being an asshole, because he wasn't actually that different from me.
Like, by definition.
He seems alright as Arquius though. At least it keeps him busy, obsessing over his muscles, asking for milk and shit like that.
I guess so.
It certainly worked out for you in my universe.
It definitely is.
Tinkering with your own mind, or identity or whatever... it's a dark road to go down.
There are enough splinters of everyone running around out there as it is, just as a natural byproduct of our reality. For me in particular. Probably for you too, as a time player.
That process doesn't need to be encouraged or fucked with.
You mean the porn stuff?
Naturally.
That sounds...
Oddly rewarding.
I mean, not to say he wasn't still a douche.
But as a pastime, cultivating a group of earnest, erotic puppet-loving chatbots sounds so much more relaxing than painstakingly constructing a version of your own brain, and then arguing with it for years thereafter.
Almost like tending to a little flock of pigeons.
_
150. DS28: =009818
Sounds about right.
We really don't have to talk about him anymore though, if it is going to stir up more bad shit for you.
Ok.
Well, in sixteen years, if you need someone to vent to again, let me know.
For what?
I think I get it.
And sure.
You're welcome for me existing.
I think it already is.
_
151. DS29: =009819
Yeah.
Well like I said, any time you want to know more, feel free to ask.
A thing?
That does sound like a Roxy thing.
Does it by any chance involve asking a rapid-fire series of questions, some of which end up being a bit too personal or invasive?
Then I guess I will disclaim in advance that I don't have any, and I don't care about yours even if you do.
Cool.
So how do we start.
Whose lightning round is this, mine or yours?
Ok.
How...
Did...
He, um,
Come to "adopt" you?
I see.
So you decided to ditch those shades for the aviator glasses?
Wait...
THE Stiller?
Incredible.
Also, such a shame what happened to that poor man.
I can tell you when it's your lightning round.
Or mine. Whatever. I'm still not sure whose lightning round it is when you're the one asking questions.
Ok. Anyway, didn't mean to interrupt.
We did that too.
Except I had to send things through time.
Always had to figure out stuff small enough to send through the sendificator, even if it was piece by piece.
Once I deliberately and quite literally sent a rabbit through time.
It was a robot.
He was a loyal friend to Jane. I don't know what happened to him though.
I hear you, man.
Hm.
You say he owned Cal as well?
Did he come down to Earth on a meteor with Cal too?
Yeah.
But if I came to Earth on a meteor the same way you all did, then I guess I just got dunked right in the fucking ocean.
Which makes sense. One of my earliest memories is of using Cal as a flotation device.
So he sorta saved my life in a way. I guess I bonded with him too, the way your bro did, even if that sounds a bit stupid.
Then again, it didn't help matters much that I lived alone in the middle of the ocean. He was my only real life friend. I mean, until I built some new ones. 
Ok.
How did your bro die?
I hate stupid surprises.
So, you said he "trained" you.
I'm guessing that means he knew what was coming?
Or, some things about your future, at least?
What?
Um,
Not to be too much of a wet blanket on that rad as fuck anecdote, but that sounds kind of far fetched.
That's not far fetched. It was pretty straightforward.
I think I just found a building poking out of the water, climbed up, then I just started foraging for food in there like a feral infant.
Supplies which I'm sure your adult self must have left behind for me, seeing as he clearly must have known some things about the future too.
Speaking of which, maybe it's your turn now?
_
152. DS30: =009820
He was deemed a heretic, and was crucified on the Washington Monument by some clowns.
Due to his dedication to freedom and peace, he came to be seen as a martyr, and then a holy figure.
He was left on the monument as an example to all, but thousands of faithful gathered below to gaze up at his pious, sort of gaunt face.
For years thereafter, his followers would carve stone busts of him in his memory, capturing the piercing glare of his final expression.
But they were all smashed to pieces by the presidential church.
That religious movement didn't last very long.
Rumor has it the batterwitch had a lot of experience crushing righteous insurrections.
Yeah. There was a whole series of final insults that led to his active rebellion, instead of just producing subversive media.
At one point, the witch "remastered" all of his films to clean up all the shitty artifacts, and released them in stunning high-def quality all over the world, using a rational business model and everything.
That REALLY set him off.
Yes. Same one.
And yeah, he teamed up with Rose from the same era.
They supposedly put up a good fight, but both died.
I have no idea.
I really don't know John at all, or any of your friends.
I know Jane was the heiress to the Crocker brand. Uh, obviously? It is her name after all.
Was John the heir to that empire in his universe?
I'd like to get to know him.
Not to mention Rose and Jade. Would have been nice to hang out and chat, in a circumstance where we weren't supposed to prepare for an imminent deadly struggle.
Huh?
Ah.
Right, I was kind of nervous about lingering there for more than a minute too.
Mainly because of Jake.
I didn't want to make him uncomfortable.
I think I have done enough of that.
Nah, sounds about right.
Seems like John was your close buddy growing up, and Jake was mine.
Yes. A lot of buddy troubles.
I vaguely touched on it earlier. I was a really bad influence in his life.
A lot of things, that were mostly my fault.
Basically, I think I bullied him into dating me.
Although I had plenty of "help" from my Auto-Responder.
There were a lot of insane plans that he hatched on my behalf.
But in fairness, I went along with them.
To this day, I can't really tell how much of that bullshit was his doing, and how much was mine, which I've just covered up through denial or selective memory.
Yeah.
That didn't last long though.
It was really lopsided and kind of forced.
What?
Oh yeah.
I forgot we weren't doing that.
_
153. DS31: =009821
Anyway, carry on. You were asking about adult Dave?
His early life isn't well documented.
There's hardly anything to read about him until he broke into show business with a few obscure projects at the turn of the century.
It all snowballed from there.
Heh.
Right.
There's certainly a lot of lore to work with.
Urban legends and stuff.
Like, through a shitty cardboard booth?
You know, like the one from the fuckin' Charlie Brown comics.
"This is what the refrance," FYI.
It sounds to me like you've been reading up on the urban legends already.
_
154. DS32: =009822
It sounds like he knew a lot of people, at least later in life.
This seems likely.
Like what?
Paleontology?
Not that I recall.
Yeah, like the porn bots.
Maybe some day, when we're both old men, you can live a quiet life tending to your fossils, and I will do the same with my dear collection of simple-minded chat robots fixated on puppet ass.
What was the lightning round question this stemmed from again?
I forget.
Maybe.
You sure you don't have anything else before we say it's officially deteriorated?
My prince gear.
You know. Leggings, slippers, the poofy asshole pants, a hood with some sort of cloth tiara deal embedded in it.
Basic stuff for princes, apparently.
I thought I hated it at first.
But over the couple hours I spent flying back, with time to think about all sorts of stuff...
It kinda grew on me.
The asshole pants are pretty damn comfortable, so I dunno if I even care how stupid they look.
And I *am* kind of an asshole, after all. So who am I to complain.
Nah. I'm sure I'll wear regular stuff again at some point.
If a shirt with a hat on it can be deemed regular.
I...
Yeah.
That page costume.
I'd have commented on it, except that would've been casting a stone through a particularly fragile glass wardrobe.
So... I just flew away.
Hm.
What?
About what?
The personal stuff?
That's fine.
?
What does this have to do with me and Jake?
Like what?
...
_
155.