Act 1
_
Act 2
_
Act 3
_
Intermission
_
Act 4
_
Act 5
_
1. KV1: =003910
wHaT iS uUuUuP mY iNvErTeBrOtHeR?NoT a MoThErFuCkInG tHiNg BrO.
oThEr ThAn I bE cHeCkIn OuT hOw My BeSt MoThErFuCkIn FrIeNd Is At Yo.
YoU SaY iT pReTtY mUcH eVeRy TiMe We TaLk YeAh.
but uh, i don't have to...
uhhh see?
but i mean man this feels so motherfuckin unnatural and shit.
YoU jUsT gOt To Be GoInG wItH wHaT fEeLs RiGhT aT wHeRe YoUr HeArT's Up In, YoU kNoW?
bEsT fRiEnD.
It'S sUcH a BeAuTiFuL tHiNg.
ThIs TrOlL dIsEaSe CaLlEd FrIeNdShIp.
iT's A mIrAcLe.
MaN eVeRyWhErE i LoOk...
aLlS i SeE iS mOtHeRfUcKiN mIrAcLeS.
It'S sO sPiRiTuAl, AlL tHeSe mIrAcLeS aNd ShIt.
oK lIkE jUsT bE tAkIn tHiS fUcKiN tItS bOtTlE oF fUcKiN fAyGo I jUsT cRaCkEd Up OpEn.
AnD hOw It'S bEiNg AlL lIkE hIsSiNg AnD sHiT.
mOtHeRfUcKiN hIsSiNg MaN, wHo WeNt AlL aNd ToLd It To Do ThAt?
HoW wOuLd It EvEn Do ThAt, It'S cRaZy.
iT's A mIrAcLe.
No No BrO, i DoN't WaNnA kNoW, dOn'T eVeN tElL mE.
kNoWiNg ShIt JuSt StEaLs Up AlL tHe FuCkIn MaGiC fRoM mY mIrAcLeS lIkE a MoThErFuCkIn ThIeF.
AnD tHaT aIn'T cOoL.
sEe MaN, i Am StRaIgHt Up TeLlInG yOu.
MiRaClEs.
iT's LiKe, AlRiGhT, cOmPuTeRs, RiGhT?
WhAt ThE fUcK?
mIrAcLeS iS wHaT.
AnYwAy WhAt'S uP wItH yOuR bAd SeLf, FoR sErIoUs HeRe.
iSn'T sOmEtHiNg BiG aLl GoInG dOwN?
i HeArD sOmEtHiNg bIg WaS gOiNg AlL dOwN.
JuSt AlL bE tElLiNg Me AlL wHaT mOtHeRfUcKiN iT's Up AnD aLl AbOuT.
yEaH!! fUcK yEaH mAn, So MyStErIoUs.
I'm NeVeR bEiNg GeTtInG cEaSeD tO bE aMaZeD bY aLl ThEsE fUcKiN mYsTeRiEs LiFe'S gOt FoR uS.
yEaH mAyBe BuT hE's YoUr BeSt FrIeNd ThOuGh So It'S aLl CoOl.
AnYwAy I tHoUgHt ThIs SoUnDeD lIkE a PrEtTy BiG mOtHeRfUcKiN dEaL mY mAn.
aAaUuUhHh...
Aw BrO nEvErMiNd, I jUsT fUcKiN dId LiKe To ScArE tHe ShIt OuTtA mYsElF hErE.
tHeSe DaMn HoRnS.
MaN yOu KnOw YoU wAnNa GiVe My HoRnS a GoOd SqUeEzE. :o)
hAhAhAhA yOu fUcKiN gOt It BrOtHeR!
_
2. TP1: =003924
hEy YeAh ThAt SoUnDs LiKe ThE mOtHeRfUcKiN sHiT's BiTcHtItS!
:o) hOnK
sO iS tHiS tHe GaMe I'vE hEaRd AbOuT?
ThE bIg MyStErY?
wHoA oK uHhH...
ThIs Is GoInG tO bE fUcKiN iNsAnE.
bUt CaN wE pLaY a LiTtLe LaTeR?
I'm OuTsIdE kEePiNg An EyE oUt HeRe FoR tHe OlD gOaT.
yOu KnOw HoW iT iS wItH fAmIlY.
Oh YeAh...
sOoOoOoOrY.
AnYwAy I'lL gO iNsIdE iN a WhIlE, wHy DoN't YoU gEt KaRkAt To FiRe Up ThAt MoThErFuCkEr WiTh YoU?
hE lIkEs GaMeS.
AlRiGhT, wElL i'Ll TrY tO gEt In AnD gEt Up On My ChIlL rEaL sOoN aNd We CaN pLaY.
jUsT gIvE mE a MiNuTe!
WhAt?
oH mAn SoRrY.
I sPaCeD oUt, DiD yOu KnOw HoW bEaTuFuL tHe SoUnD oF tHe OcEaN iS?
hAvE yOu EvEr EvEn SeEn ThE oCeAn?
oR i MeAn SmElLeD iT...
SoRrY.
_
3. TP2: =003956
COPY OF CONVERSATION TP1: =003924
_
4. TN1: =004023
mOtHeRfUcK mY bRoThEr, Im So SoRrY i KiNd Of ZoNeD oUt ThErE.
AlRiGhT, fUcK yEaH, iT's AlL gOoD aNyWaY.
i JuSt ZoNeD oUt WhEn I wAs SuPpOsEd To Be AlL aBoUt BeInG tO tElL yOu YoU'rE aLl On My TeAm.
ShIt MoThErFuCkIn YeAh My WiCkEd MoThErFuCkEr!
:o) hOnK hOnK hOnK
:o) HoNkHoNkHoNkHoNkHoNk
hAhAh FuUuUuCk, YoU sToLe My FuCkIn NoSe BrO!
WhAt GoT yOu EvEn Up ThE gUmPtIoN tO aLl FuCkIn Do ThE sHiT lIkE tHaT?
hAhAhAhA.
YeAh, I cOuLd KiCk ThE sHiT oUt Of SoMe RhYmEs BrO.
aLl StIr Up SoMe FuCkIn HeLl MiRtH aNd RiP oPeN a FuCkIn BaG oF hArShWhImSy.
YeAh! FuCk YeAh, ThAt Be HoW sHiT's AlL uSuAlLy Up AnD fUcKiN lOcKeD bRo.
bUt FiRsT hErE's ThE tHiNg WiTh ThE gAmE.
YeAh Ok If I rEmEmBeR rIgHt ThIs Is HoW wE'rE jUgGlInG tHiS sHiT.
lOt'S oF fUcKiN bAlLs In ThE aIr, HaHaHa.
TeReZi CoNnEcTeD tO kArKaT, sO hE's FuCkIn ChIlL.
tHeN i'M sUpPoSeD tO cOnNeCt To HeR sOoN tO gEt HeR aLl ChIlL tOo.
BuT sHe'S iN tHe WoOdS dOiNg SoMeThInG.
wHeN sHe CoMeS bAcK sHe StArTs PlAyInG.
So In ThE mEaN mOtHeRfUcKiN tImE i'M sUpPoSeD tO gEt YoU tO cOnNeCt To Me.
bUt I fUcKiN sPaCeD oUt AnD fOrGoT.
BeCaUsE i GuEsS i WaS wAy ToO mOtHeRfUcKiN cHiLl AlL uP iN tHiS sHiT, hAhAhAhAhA!
sO jUsT dOwNlOaD tHiS mOtHeRfUcKeR i'M sEnDiNg YoU sO wE cAn KiCk ThIs BiTcH dOwN tHe StAiRs.
AwWwWw BrOtHeR nOw YoU aLl FuCk AnD uP aNd DoNe It.
yOu ArE fUcKiN wHeEl DeEp In A bIg SlOpPy MaSsAcRe PiE tOpPeD wItH mOtHeRfUcKiN wHiPpEd RhYmE.
HoW sTrIcT aRe ThOsE bEaTs At, MoThErFuCkEr?
gOd DaMn!!!
TeLl Me MoRe WhIlE i GeT mY rEaCh On FoR tHiS fRoStY bReW.
fUuUuCk, So FuCkIn FrEsH.
YoU nEeD tO bE sLaPpEd FuCkIn SiLlY wItH a MoUtH lIkE tHaT! hAhA.
oK i WiLl.
JuSt LeT mE sNeAk Up On ThIs BoTtLe Of FaYgO aNd SnAp ItS nEcK lIkE iM a FuCkIn LaUgHsSaSsIn.
oK.
ArE tHoSe BeAtS sTiLl ChIlL?
aRe ThEy MoThErFuCkIn StRiCt???
AiGhT.
cRaCk......
HiSsSsSsSsSsSsSs.
mOtHeRfUcKiN kIcK iT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
_
5. EZ1: =004121
hAhA, fUcK yEaH, oNlY eVeRy MoThErFuCkIn DaY bRo!
MoThErFuCkIn SpIlL iT, dOn'T bE aLl KeEpIn ThAt ShIt BoTtLeD uP
lIkE a FuCkIn AlL sHaKeD uP bOtTlE oF fAyGo.
FuCk DoGg I'm ThIrStY.
i'M dOwN tO mY lAsT bOtTlE aNd I dOn'T fUcKiN kNoW iF i CaN gEt AnYmOrE iN tHiS mOtHeRfUcKiN mAgIc LaNd So I dOn'T kNoW.
ThAt'S cOoL, i CaN't AlL bE mAkInG nOt EvErYbOdY hApPy AlL tHe TiMe.
iF wE eVeR mEt I cOuLd BaKe YoU a FuCkIn PiE aNd We CoUlD cHiLl AnD mAyBe We'D bE bEtTeR bRoS tHaT wAy.
WhOaAaA, i WiLl?
hOw Do YoU kNoW tHaT?
Oh, AlRiGhT bRoThEr.
yOu MoThErFuCkIn GoT iT.
yEaH.
I mEaN, yOu GoT tO sHoW sOmE fAiTh In YoUr FrIeNdS, cAuSe ThEy'Re AlL tHe OnEs WhO'rE bEiNg To LoOk OuT fOr YoU.
sO fUcK iF yOu SaY i'M nOt DoInG tHe ShIt RiGhT, tHeN wHaT tHe MoThErFuCk Do I kNoW!
aWw, No WoRrIeS!
hAhAhA. oK.
oK, i CaN tRy, BuT mAn I dOn'T kNoW iF i KnOw HoW tO bE lIkE a BeTtEr MoThErFuCkEr ThAn AnY oThEr MoThErFuCkEr.
WoW, wHaT?
uHhHhHh.
yEaH!
fUcK yEaH. i'M aLl Up In ThE fUcKiN sHiT oF tHiS wIcKeD mYsTiCaL mOtHeRfUcKeR.
i BoNkEd An ImP oN tHe HeAd WiTh A cLuB.
AnD tHeN a LiTtLe LaTeR i ScArEd OnE wItH a HoRn.
:o)
wElL yEaH, tHeY'rE uNdErLiNgS.
AnD tHeRe'S SoMe SuBjUgGlAtIoN iNvOlVeD fOr FuCkIn SuRe!
bUt NoW wE kInD oF sEtTlEd DoWn AnD mE aNd ThE iMpS aRe ShArInG sOmE pIe
tHeSe MoThErFuCkErS aRe PrEtTy DoPe AcTuAlLy, I lIkE tHeM.
aW sHiT bRo, I dOn'T wAnT tO bE aLl LiKe To DiSaPpOiNt YoU!
WhAt CaN i Do To MaKe A bRoThEr FuCkIn ShApE hIs ShIt Up?
iF i CoUlD mAkE yOu SmIlE iT'd Be ThE bEsT fUcKiN mIrAcLe I eVeR dId PaRt Of.
hOnK hOnK hOnK! :o)
UuUhHhHhH.
yOu MeAn LiKe RoLe PlAyInG?
i'Ll TrY, bUt I'm NoT mUcH fUcKiN aNy GoOd At It I tHiNk.
oK.
uH, hEy YoU, dOn'T gO nEaR tHe MoThErFuCkIn OcEaN, cAuSe I aLl ToLd YoU nOt To A bUnCh Of TiMeS!
ShIt Is StRaIgHt Up DaNgErOuS, aNd I'm GeTtInG mY hArSh On AbOuT iT.
aLrIgHt, WeLl, WhAt ArEn'T yOu AlL nOt SuPpOsEd To Do?
WhAt KiNd Of MiScHiEf Do YoU gEt YoUr BaD fUcKiN sElF uP tO?
uMmMm, Ok WeLl.
DoN't Be DoIn AlL tHoSe BaD fUcKiN tHiNgS bRo!
cUt ThAt ShIt OuT, i'M sO aLl MeAnInG tHiS! hAhAhA.
Uh.
%?
oHhH.
fUcK mAn, I aM sO mOtHeRfUcKiN sAlTy AbOuT aLl ThAt BuSiNeSs YoU sAiD!
FuUuUuCk, Im LiKe AlL mOvInG mY mOuTh AnD tHe WiCkEd NoIsE iS cOmInG oUt In ThE fRoNtIeSt WaY pOsSiBlE.
aNd It'S gOiNg At YoUr DiReCtIoN, cAuSe ThAt'S tHe DiReCtIoN tO fUcKiN bE aNgRy At!
hAhA, nO pRoBlEm BrO.
It'S cOoL wE cOuLd AlL uP aNd MoThErFuCkIn OpEn Up A lItTlE bIt WiTh EaCh OtHeR.
lIkE bRoS.
If ThErE's StUfF yOu WaNt To GeT oFf YoUr ChEsT dUdE, lIkE i SaId I'm FuCkIn HeRe FoR a MoThErFuCkEr.
kInD oF lIkE a MiRaClE, hOw It'S aLwAyS tHeRe.
It NeVeR gOeS aWaY, yOu KnOw?
sUrE! :oD
mAn, Me ToO. i DoN't KnOw WhAt Of FuCkIn WhAt CoLoR iS wHaT, sO i DoN't BoThEr WiTh ThInKiN oN tHaT mOtHeRfUcKeR.
WoW, i GoT nO fUcKiN cLuE wHaT yOu'Re TaLkInG aBoUt
wHo Is ShE?
_
6. EA1: =004375
He's bUsY BeInG SlApPeD MoThErFuCkIn sEnSeLeSs bY ThE GuY WhO LiKeS KnIvEs
BuT I CaN ReLaY WhAt mEsSaGe yOu gOt, My bRoThEr
HaHa, YeAh i fEeL YoU, hE'S PrEtTy wOrKeD Up tOo
BeCaUsE OuR GoOd bRo sOlLuX JuSt kIcKeD ThE WiCkEd mOtHeRfUcKiN ShIt
YeAh :o(
YeAh i'd sAy tHaT An aSsHoLe iS ThE ThInG ThAt jUsT AbOuT WhAt eVeRyBoDy fEeLs lIkE
KaRkAt bLaMeS HiMsElF On iT, pOoR MoThErFuCkEr
BuT I ToLd hIm tO Be cHiLl
BeCaUsE ThErE Is a mIrAcLe cOmInG, i cAn fEeL It
i'Ve gOt tO BeLiEvE At wHaT My hEaRt tElLs iN Me, EvEn iF It's a fAkE ThInG
HoNk
UuUuH, i cAn't rEaLlY ThInK AbOuT InTeRvEnInG, tHe bLaCk fRoWnInG MoThErFuCkEr kInDa sCaReS Me
ArE YoU SuRe i cAn't hElP A bRoThEr Up iNtO HiS MoThErFuCkIn cHiLl?
BrO My aDvIcE Is yOu jUsT KiCk bAcK AnD MoThErFuCkIn sNaP InTo sOmE RuDe eLiXiR AnD MaYbE GeT YoUr wIcKeD ZoNe oN
ThErE I SaId mY PeAcE
MoThErFuCkIn cHuG ThAt sHiT LiKe yOu aNd tHe bOtTlE WaS ReUnItEd lOvErS
YeAh mAn SlAm A FaYgO
ArE YoU MoThErFuCkIn sUrE AbOuT ThAt?
YoU SeE MaN
MoThEr
FuCkIn
MiRaClEs
:o)
_
Act 5 Act 2
_
7. TP3: =004529
YeAh iM NoT FoLlOwInG ThIs mOtHeRfUcKiN PlAn uP At aLl
wHo aRe wE TrOlLiNg
oH
WeLl mOtHeR FuCk i gUeSs
oKaY
HoNk :o)
wHoA
_
8. =004692
SEE LOG FOR "Past Karkat: Wake Up" IN GAMES FOLDER
_
9. DS1: =004718
AlRiGhT My pInKeSt oF MoThErFuCkIn sTaR MoNkEyS
ArE YoU ReAdY
To gEt tHe hOrNs yOu dOnT HaVe
CoNfIsCaTeD AlL LiKe tHe mOtHeRfUcKiN HoNkTrAbAnD ThEy aRe
BeInG AlL IlLiCiT As tHe vAsT JoKe iTsElF
AnD ThEn
HaNdEd aT RiGhT BaCk tO YoU?
HaHa, SeE BrO, tHiS Is hOw i rOlL
I SuPpLy tHe hOrNs tOwArD YoU, mEtApHoRiCaLlY SpEaKiNg
SeE, lIkE
ThAt's kInD Of a tRoLl mEtApHoR
YoU GeTtInG YoUr hOrNs aLl hAnDeD To yOu, If yOu pEePs aNaToMiCaLlY WeRe sUcH To bE LiKe tHaT
DoInG ThAt's tO MeAn lIkE YoU GoT MoThErFuCkIn sAsSeD OuT
As iN TrOlLeD
BuT BrO WhEn i tElL ThAt nOiSe aT YoU
Im lIkE DoInG
A DoUbLe mEtApHoR AlL ThE WaY
AcRoSs sKaIa :o)
BeCaUsE My hOrNs iM AlL AbOuT ArE ThEsE FuNnY HoNk hOrNs InStEaD oF hEaD hOrNs
LiKe wHaT DoEs cLoWnS UsE
AnD WhEn i'm aLl tO InViTe yOu tO GeT A LiTtLe mOtHeRfUcKiN SqUeEzE On
It'lL Be a dOwNeD In, StRaIgHt fLaT, bOaRd sIdEd mIrAcLe iF YoU DoN'T GeT ScArEd sHiTtEnT ClOwNcArS
ThAt's hOw wE PlAy tHe mOtHeRfUcKiN GaMe
HoNk hOnK >:o)
WhOa, I WaS?
ShIt, I MuSt hAvE GoT To nOt rEmEmBeRiNg tHiS SoMeHoW
AwW MoThErFuCk, No :o(
I MoSt sUrElY wOuLd gEt mY ReMeMbEr oN FoR A BiTcHtItS TiMe hAd lIkE ThAt
My mInD'S NoT ThAt sHaRp nOw tHoUgH, iT'S BeEn aGeS SiNcE I HaD A GoOd pIe
DoGg, I DoN'T KnOw tHaT Im aT A PlAcE To eVeN CoNtEmPlAtE FoR EnTeRtAiNiNg tHaT KiNd oF ThInG
I DoN'T GeT TiMe
I WaSn't tHe dUdE Of tImE
I WaS ThE
ThE MoThErFuCkIn
BaRd oF
FuCk
I FoRgOt :o(
nO
Oh, MaN
ThIs sOuNdS AmAzInG, i cAn't sEe hOw i wOuLdN'T Be aLl kIcKiNg tHe wIcKeD ShIt oUt Of sUcH KiNdS Of oPpOrTuNiTiEs
:oO
_
10. KV3: =005258
honk.
HONK.
honk.
HONK.
honk.
HONK.
shut up.
I SAID SHUT THE MOTHERFUCK UP, MOTHERFUCKER.
honk honk honk :o)
HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA.
uh, yeah...
I GUESS I'M ALL MOTHERFUCKIN WEIRDING OUT AT SOME EXTENT TO MY OWN MOTHERFUCKIN SELF.
but it's all good, i'm chill with it.
ON TOP OF MOTHERFUCKIN WHAT, MOTHERFUCKER.
heh heh.
SLIME?
there is no more slime, brother.
AND ANYWAY.
shit was motherfuckin poison, didn't you know?
THEN GET MOTHERFUCKIN SCHOOLFED ALL ABOUT THE WICKED NEWS, PUNCHLINE BLOODED MOTHERFUCKER.
it rots you.
RUSTS YOUR MOTHERFUCKIN THINK PAN.
and the floor all stares up back at you through the motherfuckin hole.
BUT THERE IS NO HOLE NOW.
only under motherfuckin standing of who all i was made out to be all along.
ONLY UNDER MOTHERFUCKING STANDING OF WHO ALL I WAS MADE OUT TO MOTHERFUCKING BE ALL A MOTHERFUCKING LONG.
i've been kicking the wicked ignorance on this shit.
BEEN MOTHERFUCKIN SLAUGHTERING THE WICKED IGNORANCE, BRO.
all up in lifelong denial about my calling.
AS A DESCENDANT OF THE HIGH MOTHERFUCKIN SUBJUGGLATORS.
we are higher than you, brother.
WE ARE HIGHER THAN MOTHERFUCKIN EVERYBODY.
honk.
and now i'm the last one, so i finally motherfuckin understand.
I FINALLY GOT MY MOTHERFUCKING UNDERSTAND ON TO WHO THE MIRTHFUL MESSIAHS ARE.
they were always both me. :o)
AND ALSO MOTHERFUCKING ME. Do:
and now.
AND MOTHERFUCKING NOW.
i am going to motherfuckin kill all you motherfuckers.
I AM GOING TO MOTHERFUCKING KILL ALL YOU MOTHERFUCKERS.
and paint the wicked pictures with your motherfuckin blood.
FROM YOUR VEINS WILL DRIP MY MIRACLES.
your crushed bones will make my special stardust.
WELCOME TO THE DARK CARNIVAL, BROTHER.
honk.
HONK.
honk.
HOOOOOOOOOOONK.
_
11. KV4: =005260
HeY BeSt fRiEnD.
nOw wHaT ThE MoThEr fUcK WiLl i bE SuPpOsEd tO Do?
i'M nOt FoLlOwInG.
YeAh, I CaN DeFiNiTeLy cArRy oUt tHaT OrDeR, bRo.
i gUeSs i'lL WaIt uNtIl tHe mOtHeRfUcKiN FuTuRe hApPeNs tO SeE AbOuT WhAt aLl tHiS MuRdErInG NoIsE Is. :o)
_
12. KV5: =005261
honk.
HEY BEST MOTHERFUCKING FRIEND.
what all seems to be the motherfuckin problem? :o)
THAT'S KICKIN THE WICKED MOTHERFUCKIN MISINFORMATION, MY BROTHER.
i'm as chill as all what's can be.
NO CAUSE FOR ALARM, JUST MOTHERFUCKIN GONNA SIT AND ZONE THE MOTHERFUCK OUT WITH A PAN RUSTING PIE LIKE AS MY USUAL MOTHERFUCKIN SELF DOES.
honk.
HONK.
honk.
HONK.
i'm in your future, best friend.
I KNOW WHERE YOU MOTHERFUCKING ARE.
and what you'll motherfuckin do.
AND ALSO.
and also.
GUESS MOTHERFUCKIN WHAT.
i'm all about to be meeting up some friends. :o)
GOING TO GET PRETTY MOTHERFUCKING FRIENDLY AT THEM REAL SOON.
i wonder if you can all be at with me in time and make me get my reconsider on?
MAYBE SPLIT AN ELIXIR LIKE A COUPLE OF CHOICE BROS.
just like we are... :o)
ME AND HIM. Do:
hoooooooooooooooooonk. ;oD
_
13. KV6: =005327
honk.
_
14. EZ2: =005338
heheh.
CHECK IT THE MOTHERFUCK OUT.
it's the peasantblood.
HEH HEH.
fuckin heh.
if your blood.
IS A RUNNING MOTHERFUCKING GAG.
then soon.
IT WILL BE RUNNING.
through my motherfucking fingers.
you'll...
KNEEL. >:o)
i'll show you what i motherfuckin got.
IF YOU SHOW ME WHAT'S MOTHERFUCKIN YOURS.
it was.
A MOTHERFUCKING.
joke.
HONK.
you really should kneel.
I SAID.
kneel motherfucker.
I TOLD YOU TO MOTHERFUCKING KNEEL, MOTHERFUCKER.
_
15. TN2: =005886
If mOtHeRfUcKiN MaGiC'S AlL We'vE EvEr kNoWn aT
ThEn iT'S EaSy tO Be mIsSiN WhAt bE FuCkIn tHe hApS
BuT I'M AlL ScOpIn aT MiRaClEs tHaT ArE Up iN ThE AiR
GoT My sEe oN Of mIrAcLeS, tHeY'Re hErE AnD ThEy'rE ThErE
I Be cHeCkIn tHe mIrAcLeS WhIlE FaLlInG DoWn sTaIrS
SeEn tHe sHiT OuT A MiRaClEs tHaT ArE AlL BeInG Up aT BaSiCaLlY PrEtTy mUcH EvErYwHeRe, FuCk...
OcEaNs oF FaYgO FuCkIn gLiTtEr lIkE SpAcE
A FiSt fUlL Of sTaRdUsT'S WhAt's pOoFiN My fAcE
A MiLlIoN HoRnS HoNkIn rAcKeTs iN PiLeS
A OnE WhEeL DeViCe wHaT CaN RoCkEt iN StYlE
Is sHiT ThAt wHaT I WiSh fOr
BeCaUsE... (MoThErFuCkIn cHoRuS BrO)
I'M AlL A FiRm bElIeVeR At tHe mIrAcLeS
Do yOu hAvE TiMe fOr mY MiRaClEs, BrOtHeR :o)
Do yOu gEt yOuR NoTiCe oN Of tHe mIrAcLeS
So mAnY FuCkIn mIrAcLeS, tHe mAgIc mOtHeRfUcKiN MiRaClEs
HoNk.
AhAhA, yEaH, bRo? 
MoThErFuCk dUdE, yOu bEsT UnDeRsTaNd i gOt mOrE SlAmS In mE.
ThEy bE As fOrEvEr aS My lImItLeSs fAiTh iN AlL My bElIeViNgS AnD ShIt.
BuT WhAt i mOtHeRfUcKiN NeEd, My bRoThEr...
AsIdE Of pLoWiNg nOsE FuCkInG FiRsT InTo a bItChIn pAn oF TeNaCiOuS MuCiLaGe
Is tO ChEcK OuT WhAt sLaMs yOu cAn sTiCk iN My dUcTs!
HaHa, FuCkIn dRoP It bRo!
DrOp iT LiKe yOu sPaCeD OuT AnD FoRgOt yOu wErE HoLdInG It iN ThE FiRsT MoThErFuCkIn pLaCe.
ShIiIiIiIiIiIt. 
SlAm iT LiKe a fUcKiN DoOr bY AcCiDeNt oN SoMeThInG ThAt hUrTs!!!
HoNkHoNkHoNkHoNkHoNk.
GoD DaAaAaAaAaAaAaMn. YoU ArE DeAlIn sOmE HeArTy rEpRoAcH ToNiGhT.
FlYiNg fUcKiN HiGh, MaN.
HiGhEr tHaN A LaUgHsAsSiN Up oN ThE MoThErFuCkIn gRiEf tRaPeZe.
HiGhEr tHaN A SuBjUgGlAtOr gEtTiN HiS WeEp oN FoR ThE VaSt hOnK I BeLiEvE In tO CoMe.
No bRo i'm sErIoUs, YoUr rHyMeS ArE FlY As tHe mOsT WiCkEd pIeCe oF ShIt a mIrAcLe eVeR ToOk iN ThE SkY.
SoMeOnE ClIp tHeIr mOtHeRfUcKiN WiNgS So i sTaNd a cHaNcE! wHoOpS, i mEaN SiT A ChAnCe, FuCk... 
(lOoK OuT FoR ThE HoOk bRo!!!)
GeT OfFa tHoSe wHeElS, gEt oFfA ThOsE WhEeLs.
If mIrAcLeS ArEn't fAkE He'lL GeT OfFa tHoSe wHeElS!
GeT OfFa tHoSe wHeElS, gEt oFfA ThOsE WhEeLs.
If mIrAcLeS ArEn't fAkE He'lL GeT OfFa tHoSe wHeElS!
ShIiIt,
MoThErFuCk iT, mOtHeRfUcKeR!
PuRe mAgIc iS AlL WhEn tHeRe bE HaTcHiN Of gRuBs
I'Ve sEeN ShIt tHaT WoUlD ShOcK YoUr lOoKsTuBs
I PeEpEd oN A PlAcE Of 6 tRiLlIoN HeMoS
AlL Up aT OnE RoCk, BlEeDiNg aS EqUaLs
It's eAsY To sEe iF YoU SeArCh aLl yOuR FeElInS
ThAt pEaCe hApPeNs fIrSt, AnD MuRdEr's tHe sEqUeL
It's tHe bEaUtY Of tHe cArNiVaL, tHe mAgIc's iN TeNtS
FuCkIn dArKnEsS OuTsIdE, bUt tHe lIgHt mAkEs yOu wInCe
JuSt tAkE My mOtHeR FuCkIn hAnD BrO
PuT On yOuR ShAdEs, PuLl bAcK ThE FlAp
AnD GeT OfFa tHoSe wHeElS!!!
HaHaHa fUcK MoThErFuCkIn yEaH!
LeT'S TaKe tHiS NiNjA-tItTiEd BiTcH BaCk tO ThE HiVe wItH ThE ChOrUs...
ToGeThEr mY MiRaClE BrOtHeR! 
I'M AlL A FiRm bElIeVeR At tHe mIrAcLeS 
Do yOu gEt yOuR NoTiCe oN Of tHe mIrAcLeS 
FuCk yEs, HeReS WhErE ThE SlAm tUrNs tO NoThIn bUt hOnKs...
HoNk hOnK HoNk hOnK HoNk hOnK HoNk
HoNk hOnK HoNk hOnK HoNk hOnK HoNk 
FuUuUuUuUuUuUuUuUuCk! 
YeAh, BrO. yEaH!!! 
Me tOo, BrO, yOu mOtHeR FuCkIn kNoW ThErE Be sOmE Of mY EyE's RoYaL JeLlY To gO WiTh yOuR EmOtIoNaL pEaNuT BuTtEr. 
ThIs iS BeAuTiFuL, dUdE, i fEeL So aT ChIlL WiTh yOu. 
HeY...
WhEn wE Up aNd sTaRt tO KiCk aT ThIs rEd TeAm NoIsE,
YoU ShOuLd mAkE YoUr wAy tO GeT YoUr hAnG On aT My hIvE. 
We cOuLd sPlIt a tIn oF ThE PiMpEsT SnEeZe i gOt oN HaNd, BaKeD Up aLl sPeCiAl fOr yOu.
AnD ThEn mAyBe mAkE OuT A LiTtLe. 
;o)
_
16. DS2: =005927
it's all your fault.
IT'S ALL YOUR MOTHERFUCKIN FAULT.
honk.
YOU ALL CRACKED OFF THE TOP OF THE BOTTLE TO THOSE FUCKIN CLOWN IMPOSTORS.
that all were spraying out the flagrant motherfuckin heresies at me.
THE FLAGRANT MOTHER FUCKING HERESIES MOTHER FUCKER.
is what came out from their mouths, it made me get my sadness on to see it.
AND MY RAGE ON FUCKING HARDER. 
all my life i believed at a fuckin paradise to come what held the most baller, darkest of carnivals to join.
AND A PROPHECY
to tell all about a band of rowdy and capricious minstrels steeped in the good harshwhimsy.
THE MIRTHFUL MESSIAHS WERE FORETOLD TO BE CRASHING THAT FUCKING PIE STAND AND BRING THE HOLY RUCKUS.
like a giddy fuckin ninja one wheeling head long at the hugest fuckin horn heap shangri la's got to see.
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE VAST HONK, YOU BLASPHEMOUS MOTHERFUCKER.
what i believed in it to be was so beautiful, us and them all mellowing in tents, bumpin sounds, tossing back the faygo and soaking the miracles up our faith sponges, while the special stardust rained down at our elixir sticky faces, like a bunch a fuckin fairy powder from religion space.
IT WAS GOING TO BE US AND MOTHER FUCKING THEM.
them and mother fuckin us. :o(
BUT NOW.
because of you.
BECAUSE OF ALL YOU AND YOUR FUCKING OUTRAGEOUSNESS.
you stole up all my miracles away by revealing at me how the wicked shit was really kicked.
LIKE SOME FILTHY FUCKING SCIENSTIFF WHO AT OLD TIMES WOULD BE RULED UNFUNNY WITHOUT EVEN GETTING HIS FUCKING TRIAL ON.
and now i don't know what to think about the spiritual fantasies i had.
HONK )o:
uhhhhh, what stuff?
>:o?
bro, that word you used isn't nothing real i've heard of.
IT STRIKES AT ME AS ANOTHER HERETICAL FUCKING BASTARDIZATION OF SOME SACRED SHIT I TAKE SERIOUSLY IN MY PUMP BISCUIT.
i mean i guess, took seriously.
I HAVE THE IDEA THAT YOU PUT IN MY PAN TO SIT THERE.
that the paradise planet
IS A FUCKING JOKE.
and the miracles
ARE FAKE.
pure fiction.
FALSE FAKEY FRAUDY CON JOBS FROM A BUNCH OF UNFUNNY NINJA HARLEQUIN BULLSHIT ARTISTS.
can't it be motherfuckin
BOTH THINGS.
_
17. DS3: =005928
no.
MOTHER FUCK NO, BRO.
i'm not looking on any more of your blasphmemes.
I REALLY JUST CAME BACK ON YOU TO MOTHER FUCKING SAY.
that while that sickening noise you did at me is your fault
THERE'S SOMETHING I DID AT YOU WHAT'S MINE.
i did something that's motherfucking atrocious to your posse.
MADE YOUR WHOLE CREW OF JOKERS GET TO BEING KINDA MENTALLY MOTHER FUCKIN
unstable.
IN FUCKING FACT
that atrocious business i got to doing
I DID THAT SHIT TO YOUR WHOLE UNIVERSE AS A MATTER OF MOTHER FUCKING FACT.
you see
YOU MOTHER FUCKIN SEE
i finally got all caught up in what's true behind the sweet murdermirth of the bitchin bloodcircus.
I REACHED DEEP DOWN AND GOT AT WHERE ALL THE REAL HARSHWHIMSIES WERE HIDING INSIDE ME.
in the angriest ways i found up my dark ancestral chucklevoodoos within.
AND THEN
_
18. DS4: =005929
i focused on them through the rage you made me have
AND I WENT AND MADE YOUR UNIVERSE...
_
19. DS5: =005930
terminal. Bo)
_
20. DS6: =005931
ALL THAT MOTHER FUCKIN MATTERS IS I REMEMBER YOU AND WHAT YOU DID.
i'm just all letting you in on the ways i set the high justice in motion.
MADE US MOTHERFUCKING SQUARE, YOU AND ME.
me and you.
HAHAHAHAHA, YOU DON'T MOTHER FUCKING BELIEVE.
you need to get more spirituality into your superstition ghost.
LIKE THE MOTHERFUCKING FAITHCHUMP THAT WHAT I WAS.
as if i'd forget to do my chucklevoodoos to you too.
TO FUCK UP YOUR DREAMS.
make your worst fears come alive and get up on their haunts in your naphappy pan.
YOU MOTHER FUCKING KNOW, BROTHER.
its the fuckin puppet.
THE ONE THAT'S ALL GOT TO BE MY BEST FUCKING FRIEND I GOT NOW.
now that my other buddy managed to be having his head chopped off. :oC
YOUR BRO'S DEAD BRO.
couldn't keep my new friend captive no more.
RELEASED YOUR NIGHTMARES RIGHT INTO MY WARM FUCKING EMBRACE.
and now i listen at what they whisper through my hear ducts.
I'M ALL HEARING THESE AMAZING MOTHERFUCKIN THINGS.
i think he'll help me refigure out what's the real reality about the miracles.
HE'LL HELP ME TO MOTHER FUCKIN DISCOVER THE TRUTH OF WHO THE MESSIAHS ARE.
the real messiahs, not the false mess a lies, hahahahaha.
HONK.
motherfuuuuuck yes, bro.
HE SAYS
all in this funny little voice
THAT IS SO
very
VERY
very
VERY
quiet
THAT
it's time
TO GO
mother
FUCKING
kill
THEM
all.
YEAH.
hahaha, here was i to come at you with all these unruly upbraids i got pent up.
WHEN YOU KNOW MOTHERFUCKIN WHAT?
i should be gettin grateful to you for sharing at me your way ridic heresies, brother.
THE ROAD TO THE DARK CARNIVAL HAS NEVER BEFORE BEEN PAVED WITH LOUDER HONK HORNS TO TREAD UPON.
and scare the living motherfuck out of the lowblood faithless with each step. ;o)
YOU FUCKIN KNOW IT, BRO.
i like you.
WOULDN'T MIND TAKING THAT PALE MARSHMALLOW YOU GOT AS A NUGBONE OFF YOUR SHOULDERS.
for this collection i got started on.
ADD A LITTLE STRAWBERRY JAM TO THIS PEANUT BUTTER SANDWICH I'M MAKING BETWEEN MY MOTHER FUCKING LIPS.
hey, before you go
HOW ABOUT THAT WE
slam a little. ;oD 
_
21. DoSc1*: =006009
that's all motherfuckin done white texted bro.
NOW WHAT?
oh yeah?
AND JUST WHAT THE MOTHER FUCK IS IT
that we motherfuckin are?
:o?
_
Act 6
_
Act 6 Intermission 1
_
22. KV7: =006250
honk.
HONK.
naw brother, i was just about to all say for you to try and get your settle down on, maybe.
:o(
_
Act 6 Act 2
_
Act 6 Intermission 2
_
Act 6 Act 3
_
23. JC1; Tavrisprite1: =006735
honk.
_
24. JC2; Tavrisprite2: =006735
HONK.
_
Act 6 Intermission 3
_
25. KuMa1: =007208
shut your mother fucking mouth and give me the cod piece.
_
26. RL1: =007298
yeah, i all up and motherfuckin know that already.
NO.
like i'd even give a dayglow chainsaw bitch like that on my time of day up in any quadrant.
BESIDES, ALREADY GOT MY BLACK ROM ON WITH ANOTHER MOTHERFUCKER.
been dating somebody in the motherfuckin shadows. getting pretty nasty between us. all experiencing the shit out of the dark miracle called hatebliss. 
:o)
no.
NO.
no.
HONK.
do i mother fucking look like i'd motherfuckin joke around with a mother fucker?
IT'S SIMPLE.
mother fucker.
SHE ALL GETS ON HER HATE OF ME QUITE UNDERSTANDABLY, SEEING AS TO WHAT A VILE PIECE OF CLOWN ASS TRASH I'M ALL IS.
but doesn't quite hate me enough to want to kill me. :o)
HEY.
please don't all tell at this noise to anyone.
IF KARKAT MOTHER FUCKIN KNEW ON THIS...
he actually would want to kill me. :o(
MOTHER FUCK YEAH THEY MOTHER FUCKING DO.
_
27. =007309
honk
_
28. =007310
HONK
_
29. MINISTRIFE: =007327
honk
HONK.
_
Act 6 Act 4
_
Act 6 Intermission 4
_
Act 6 Act 5
_
Act 6 Act 5 Act 2
_
Act 6 Act 5 Act 1
_
Act 6 Intermission 5
_
Act 6 Act 6
_
Act 6 Act 6 Intermission 1
_
Act 6 Act 6 Act 2
_
Act 6 Act 6 Intermission 2
_
30. ArSe1: =008451
HONK.
_
31. ArSe2: =008456
MOTHER FUCK WHO'S ALL THIS FRESH PIMP RYDA I GOT MY WICKED PEEP ON FOR SUDDENLY? IT'S A MOTHER FUCKIN NINJALICIOUS HO-TITTY MIRACLE JACKED UP IN THIS BITCH ASS MOTHER FU--
_
32. CJ1: =008565
:o)
_
33. CJ2: =008582
honk.
honk honk.
_
34. CJ3: =008583
honk.
HONK.
...
:o)
_
35. TP5: =008594
HONK.
_
36. TP6: =008596
:o)
:o)
_
37. TP7: =008676
TeReZi...
wHoA.
PlEaSe StOp.
YoU'rE mOtHeRfUcKiN...
hUrTiNg Me. :o(
_
38. TP8: =008688
 
_
39. JaEn1: =008729
;o)
_
40. KV8: =008742
honk.
_
Act 6 Act 6 Act 3
_
Act 6 Act 6 Intermission 3
_
Act 6 Act 6 Act 4
_
Act 6 Act 6 Intermission 4
_
41. KV9; TP9; JE1: =009279
*HONK*
_
42. JE2: =009281
*HONK*
_
Act 6 Act 6 Act 5
_
Act 6 Act 6 Intermission 5
_
43. =009359
HONK
_
44. =009362
HONK
_
45. =009410
HONK
_
46. =009773
HONK
_
47. =009775
HONK
_
48.